<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TEI xml:space="preserve" xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0 https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kermitt2/grobid/master/grobid-home/schemas/xsd/Grobid.xsd" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">
	<teiHeader xml:lang="en">
		<fileDesc>
			<titleStmt>
				<title level="a" type="main">General Green's function formalism for layered systems: Wave function approach</title>
				<funder ref="#_rj485Qa">
					<orgName type="full">NSFC program for "Scientific Research Center"</orgName>
				</funder>
				<funder ref="#_J3F2Stp #_W4CvCcT #_6wqC9PM #_DGsjU2p">
					<orgName type="full">NSFC</orgName>
				</funder>
				<funder ref="#_mY9tCDh #_VQmthgR">
					<orgName type="full">MOST of China</orgName>
				</funder>
				<funder>
					<orgName type="full">Beijing Computational Science Research Center</orgName>
					<orgName type="abbreviated">CSRC</orgName>
				</funder>
			</titleStmt>
			<publicationStmt>
				<publisher>American Physical Society (APS)</publisher>
				<availability status="unknown"><p>Copyright American Physical Society (APS)</p>
				</availability>
				<date type="published" when="2017-02-17">17 February 2017</date>
			</publicationStmt>
			<sourceDesc>
				<biblStruct>
					<analytic>
						<author>
							<persName><forename type="first">Shu-Hui</forename><surname>Zhang</surname></persName>
							<affiliation key="aff0">
								<orgName type="institution">Beijing Computational Science Research Center</orgName>
								<address>
									<postCode>100193</postCode>
									<settlement>Beijing</settlement>
									<country key="CN">China</country>
								</address>
							</affiliation>
						</author>
						<author>
							<persName><forename type="first">Wen</forename><surname>Yang</surname></persName>
							<affiliation key="aff0">
								<orgName type="institution">Beijing Computational Science Research Center</orgName>
								<address>
									<postCode>100193</postCode>
									<settlement>Beijing</settlement>
									<country key="CN">China</country>
								</address>
							</affiliation>
						</author>
						<author>
							<persName><forename type="first">Kai</forename><surname>Chang</surname></persName>
							<affiliation key="aff1">
								<orgName type="department">Institute of Semiconductors</orgName>
								<orgName type="laboratory">SKLSM</orgName>
								<orgName type="institution">Chinese Academy of Sciences</orgName>
								<address>
									<postBox>P.O. Box 912</postBox>
									<postCode>100083</postCode>
									<settlement>Beijing</settlement>
									<country key="CN">China</country>
								</address>
							</affiliation>
							<affiliation key="aff2">
								<orgName type="department">Synergetic Innovation Center of Quantum Information and Quantum Physics</orgName>
								<orgName type="institution">University of Science and Technology of China</orgName>
								<address>
									<postCode>230026</postCode>
									<settlement>Hefei</settlement>
									<region>Anhui</region>
									<country key="CN">China</country>
								</address>
							</affiliation>
						</author>
						<title level="a" type="main">General Green's function formalism for layered systems: Wave function approach</title>
					</analytic>
					<monogr>
						<title level="j" type="main">Physical Review B</title>
						<title level="j" type="abbrev">Phys. Rev. B</title>
						<idno type="ISSN">2469-9950</idno>
						<idno type="eISSN">2469-9969</idno>
						<imprint>
							<publisher>American Physical Society (APS)</publisher>
							<biblScope unit="volume">95</biblScope>
							<biblScope unit="issue">7</biblScope>
							<date type="published" when="2017-02-17">17 February 2017</date>
						</imprint>
					</monogr>
					<idno type="MD5">A0A54D4C223CFC1E33ECCED93D9BFB94</idno>
					<idno type="DOI">10.1103/physrevb.95.075421</idno>
					<note type="submission">Received 19 September 2016; revised manuscript received 20 January 2017;</note>
				</biblStruct>
			</sourceDesc>
		</fileDesc>
		<encodingDesc>
			<appInfo>
				<application version="0.8.0" ident="GROBID" when="2023-12-12T19:36+0000">
					<desc>GROBID - A machine learning software for extracting information from scholarly documents</desc>
					<ref target="https://github.com/kermitt2/grobid"/>
				</application>
			</appInfo>
		</encodingDesc>
		<profileDesc>
			<abstract>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><p>The single-particle Green's function (GF) of mesoscopic structures plays a central role in mesoscopic quantum transport. The recursive GF technique is a standard tool to compute this quantity numerically, but it lacks physical transparency and is limited to relatively small systems. Here we present a numerically efficient and physically transparent GF formalism for a general layered structure. In contrast to the recursive GF that directly calculates the GF through the Dyson equations, our approach converts the calculation of the GF to the generation and subsequent propagation of a scattering wave function emanating from a local excitation. This viewpoint not only allows us to reproduce existing results in a concise and physically intuitive manner, but also provides analytical expressions of the GF in terms of a generalized scattering matrix. This identifies the contributions from each individual scattering channel to the GF and hence allows this information to be extracted quantitatively from dual-probe STM experiments. The simplicity and physical transparency of the formalism further allows us to treat the multiple reflection analytically and derive an analytical rule to construct the GF of a general layered system. This could significantly reduce the computational time and enable quantum transport calculations for large samples. We apply this formalism to perform both analytical analysis and numerical simulation for the two-dimensional conductance map of a realistic graphene p-n junction. The results demonstrate the possibility of observing the spatially resolved interference pattern caused by negative refraction and further reveal a few interesting features, such as the distance-independent conductance and its quadratic dependence on the carrier concentration, as opposed to the linear dependence in uniform graphene.</p></div>
			</abstract>
		</profileDesc>
	</teiHeader>
	<text xml:lang="en">
		<body>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>I. INTRODUCTION</head><p>The single-particle retarded Green's function (GF) is a key tool to calculate local and transport properties in mesoscopic systems <ref type="bibr" target="#b0">[1,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b1">2]</ref>, such as conductance, shot noise <ref type="bibr" target="#b2">[3]</ref>, local density of states, and local currents <ref type="bibr" target="#b3">[4,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b4">5]</ref>. In the most popular scheme in which a scatterer is connected to two (or more) semi-infinite ballistic leads, the Landauer-Büttiker formula <ref type="bibr" target="#b5">[6]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b6">[7]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b7">[8]</ref> expresses the conductance σ = (e 2 /h)T (E F ) in terms of the transmission probability T (E F ) across the scatterer on the Fermi surface. Typically, the electronic structure and transport properties of a mesoscopic system are described by a lattice model with a localized basis in real space, e.g., discretization of the continuous model <ref type="bibr" target="#b8">[9]</ref>, empirical tight binding <ref type="bibr" target="#b9">[10]</ref>, or first-principles density-functional theory with a localized basis set <ref type="bibr" target="#b10">[11,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b11">12]</ref>. Then T (E F ) is constructed from the lattice GF G(E F ) across the scatterer through either an expression derived by Caroli et al. <ref type="bibr" target="#b12">[13]</ref> or the Fisher-Lee relations <ref type="bibr" target="#b13">[14]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b14">[15]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b15">[16]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b16">[17]</ref> that express the scattering matrix S(E F ) of the scatterer in terms of the lattice GF G(E F ).</p><p>The recursive GF method (RGF) is a standard tool to compute the lattice GF of a scatterer connected to multiple leads <ref type="bibr" target="#b1">[2,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b17">18]</ref>. This method is reliable, computationally efficient, and allows for a parallel implementation <ref type="bibr" target="#b18">[19]</ref>. It was pioneered by Thouless and Kirkpatrick <ref type="bibr" target="#b19">[20]</ref> and by Lee and Fisher <ref type="bibr" target="#b20">[21]</ref>. Then MacKinnon presented a "slice" formulation for a general layered system, which is the form most used nowadays * wenyang@csrc.ac.cn † kchang@semi.ac.cn <ref type="bibr" target="#b21">[22]</ref>. Variations of the method were also introduced to treat multiple leads <ref type="bibr" target="#b22">[23]</ref>, arbitrary geometries <ref type="bibr" target="#b23">[24,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b24">25]</ref>, and local scatterers inside an infinite periodic system <ref type="bibr" target="#b25">[26,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b26">27]</ref>. With the development of many numerical algorithms, such as fast recursive or iterative schemes <ref type="bibr" target="#b27">[28]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b28">[29]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b29">[30]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b30">[31]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b31">[32]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b32">[33]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b33">[34]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b34">[35]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b35">[36]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b36">[37]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b37">[38]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b38">[39]</ref> and closed-form solutions <ref type="bibr" target="#b39">[40]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b40">[41]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b41">[42]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b42">[43]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b43">[44]</ref>, the development of RGF has culminated in many packages with different focus <ref type="bibr" target="#b44">[45]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b45">[46]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b46">[47]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b47">[48]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b48">[49]</ref> and is applicable to an arbitrary lattice Hamiltonian <ref type="bibr" target="#b49">[50]</ref>. However, these techniques and our knowledge about the lattice GF still suffer from two drawbacks/limitations.</p><p>First, there are two widely used approaches in mesoscopic quantum transport: the GF approach <ref type="bibr" target="#b0">[1,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b50">51]</ref> that computes the GF G(E) and the wave function mode matching approach <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">[52]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b52">[53]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b53">[54]</ref> that computes the unitary scattering matrix S(E). However, the connection between the GF G(E) and S(E) and hence the connection between these two approaches remain incomplete. It is well known that S(E) can be constructed from G(E) through the Fisher-Lee relations (see Fig. <ref type="figure">1</ref>), as first derived by Fisher and Lee <ref type="bibr" target="#b13">[14]</ref> for a single parabolic band and two-terminal structures and later generalized to multiple leads <ref type="bibr" target="#b14">[15]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b15">[16]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b16">[17]</ref> and arbitrary lattice models <ref type="bibr" target="#b24">[25,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b40">41,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">55]</ref>. However, the inverse of this relation is nontrivial <ref type="bibr" target="#b55">[56]</ref>: explicit expressions of G(E) in terms of S(E) were derived <ref type="bibr" target="#b14">[15]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b15">[16]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b16">[17]</ref> only for a single parabolic band and in regions far from the scatterer. Generalization of this result to a general lattice model and over other regions would not only complete the equivalence <ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref> between the GF approach and the wave function mode matching approach (Fig. <ref type="figure">1</ref>), but also provides important tools to analyze the multiprobe scanning tunneling microscopy (STM), which has been applied to characterize a wide range of systems (see Refs. <ref type="bibr" target="#b56">[57,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b57">58]</ref> for recent reviews) in the past FIG. <ref type="figure">1</ref>. Connection between two widely used approaches to mesoscopic quantum transport: the GF approach and wave function mode matching approach. The former calculates the GF G(E), while the latter calculates the scattering matrix S(E). The Fisher-Lee relations allow S(E) to be constructed from G(E), while the inverse relation remains absent for a general lattice model. few years, including nanowires <ref type="bibr" target="#b58">[59]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b59">[60]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b60">[61]</ref>, carbon nanotubes <ref type="bibr" target="#b61">[62]</ref>, graphene nanoribbons <ref type="bibr" target="#b62">[63,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b63">64]</ref>, monolayer and bilayer graphene <ref type="bibr" target="#b64">[65]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b65">[66]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b66">[67]</ref>, and grain boundaries in graphene <ref type="bibr" target="#b67">[68,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b68">69]</ref> and copper <ref type="bibr" target="#b69">[70]</ref>. With one STM probe at R 1 and the other STM probe at R 2 , the Landauer-Büttiker formula expresses the conductance between the STM probes in terms of the GF G(R 2 ,R 1 ,E F ), which provides spatially resolved information about the sample; e.g., with an analytical expression for the GF of pristine graphene <ref type="bibr" target="#b25">[26,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b26">27]</ref>, Settnes et al. <ref type="bibr" target="#b70">[71]</ref> were able to identify the different scattering processes of local scatterers in graphene. However, this analysis is still qualitative. To go one step further to extract quantitatively the information about the scatterers, an explicit expression of the GF in terms of the scattering matrix is required.</p><p>Second, the time cost of RGF increases rapidly with the number of localized basis required to subtend the sample. This imposes a computational limit when addressing realistic experimental samples; e.g., many quantum transport studies on graphene consider narrow graphene "nanoribbons" rather than large-area graphene. Three methods have been proposed to lift this constraint. The modular RGF <ref type="bibr" target="#b16">[17,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b35">36,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b71">72]</ref> is limited to electrons in a single parabolic band and specific shape of the sample. The other two methods essentially reduce the number of transverse bases, either by projecting the system Hamiltonian onto a small number of transverse modes <ref type="bibr" target="#b72">[73]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b73">[74]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b74">[75]</ref> or by assuming translational invariance <ref type="bibr" target="#b75">[76]</ref> along the transverse direction. They could significantly reduce the time cost for wide samples, but the time cost still increases linearly with the length of the scatterer (along which transport occurs).</p><p>To study a long sample, a more efficient method is desirable.</p><p>The origin of the above drawbacks/limitations is probably that the RGF treats the GF as a matrix and constructs the GF by a series of matrix recursion rules derived from the Dyson equation. Interestingly, although the rules for constructing the scattering matrix in terms of the GF (i.e., the Fisher-Lee relation) are concise and physically intuitive, their rigorous derivation (in which the GF is treated as a matrix) turns out to be rather tedious (see, e.g., Refs. <ref type="bibr" target="#b14">[15,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b15">16,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b24">25]</ref>). This somewhat surprising fact suggests the possible existence of a very different way to represent and calculate the GF. This could not only enable a straightforward physical interpretation of the final results, but also shed light on some previous debates <ref type="bibr" target="#b52">[53,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">55,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b76">77]</ref> on the relationship between different calculation techniques in mesoscopic quantum transport.</p><p>In this work, we develop a numerically efficient and physically transparent GF formalism to address the above issues in layered systems, i.e., any system that is nonperiodic along one direction, but is finite or periodic along the other directions. This includes a wide range of physical systems, such as interfaces and junctions, Hall bars, nanowires, multilayers, superlattices, carbon nanotubes, and graphene nanoribbons. Compared with the RGF that directly calculates the GF as a matrix through the Dyson equations, our approach converts the calculation of the GF to the generation and subsequent propagation of a scattering wave function emanating from a local excitation. This viewpoint provides several advantages. First, the procedures for calculating the GF G(E) becomes physically transparent and existing results from the RGF (such as the Fisher-Lee relation) can be derived in a concise and physically intuitive manner. Second, the GF G(E) can be readily expressed in terms of a few scattering wave functions with energy E. This provides an on-shell generalization of the standard spectral expansion in classic textbooks on quantum mechanics <ref type="bibr" target="#b77">[78]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b78">[79]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b79">[80]</ref>,</p><formula xml:id="formula_0">G(R 2 ,R 1 ,E) = λ R 1 | λ λ |R 2 /(E + i0 + -E λ )</formula><p>, which involves all the eigenstates {| λ } and eigenenergies {E λ } of the system. In terms of a generalized scattering matrix S(E) that describes the scattering of both traveling and evanescent waves, we further establish a one-to-one correspondence between G(E) and S(E) (see Fig. <ref type="figure">1</ref>). This identifies the contributions from each individual scattering channel (including evanescent channels) to the GF and hence allows this information to be extracted quantitatively from dual-probe STM. Third, the simplicity and physical transparency of the formalism further allows us to perform an infinite summation of the multiple reflection between different scatterers and arrive at an analytical construction rule for the GF of a general layered system containing an arbitrary number of scatterers. This could make the time cost independent of the length of the sample along the transport direction and hence significantly speed up the calculation. By further reducing the number of bases along the transverse direction <ref type="bibr" target="#b72">[73]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b73">[74]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b74">[75]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b75">[76]</ref>, our formalism enables quantum transport calculations over macroscopic distances and on large samples.</p><p>Recently, the chiral tunneling <ref type="bibr" target="#b80">[81]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b81">[82]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b82">[83]</ref> and negative refraction <ref type="bibr" target="#b83">[84]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b84">[85]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b85">[86]</ref> of graphene p-n junctions have received a lot of interest and the anomalous focusing effect was observed experimentally <ref type="bibr" target="#b86">[87,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b87">88]</ref>, but previous theoretical studies are mostly based on the low-energy continuous model, whose validity is limited to the vicinity of the Dirac points. Here we apply our GF approach to perform an analytical analysis and numerical simulation for the two-dimensional conductance map of dual-probe STM experiments in a realistic graphene p-n junction described by the tight-binding model. The results demonstrate the possibility of observing the spatially resolved interference pattern caused by negative refraction and further reveals some interesting features (such as the distanceindependent conductance and its quadratic dependence on the carrier concentration, as opposed to the linear dependence in uniform graphene) that may also be observed in dual-probe STM experiments.</p><p>This paper is organized as follows. In Sec. II, we introduce the model, review the commonly used RGF technique, and presents the key idea of our approach. In Sec. III, we derive the GF of an infinite system containing a single scatterer, as well as an analytical construction rule for the GF of a general layered system containing an arbitrary number of scatterers. In Sec. IV, we express the GF analytically in terms of a </p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>FIG. 2. (a)</head><p>A layered 2D structure consisting of multiple periodic slices (i.e., leads) and disordered slices (i.e., scatterers). (b) Regarding each slice as a unit cell (filled squares), the structure in (a) becomes a 1D lattice. (c) A semi-infinite lead connected to a scatterer. The unit cell Hamiltonian (filled squares) and nearest-neighbor hopping (double arrows) are m-independent inside the lead, but could be disordered inside the scatterer. generalized scattering matrix or in terms of a few scattering states on the energy shell E. In Sec. V, we exemplify our results in a 1D chain and then apply it to analyze and simulate the two-dimensional conductance map of a realistic graphene p-n junction. Finally, a brief conclusion is given in Sec. VI.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>II. THEORETICAL MODEL AND KEY IDEAS</head><p>We consider a general layered system in the lattice representation. When each layer is an infinite, periodic repetition of a basic unit, we can make a Fourier transform to effectively reduce each layer to a single basic unit. Disorder inside each layer can also be introduced by using a sufficiently large unit cell and repeating it periodically. Then we can regard each layer as a finite-size unit cell, so the system becomes a 1D lattice, e.g., by taking each layer/slice of the structure in Fig. <ref type="figure">2</ref>(a) as a unit cell, Fig. <ref type="figure">2</ref>(a) becomes Fig. <ref type="figure">2(b)</ref>. A general 1D lattice can always be decomposed into a few nonperiodic regions (referred to as scatterers) consisting of different unit cells sandwiched between periodic regions (referred to as leads) consisting of identical unit cells; see Fig. <ref type="figure">2</ref>(b) for an example.</p><p>Without losing generality, we consider nearest-neighbor hopping <ref type="bibr" target="#b88">[89]</ref> and use M m to denote the number of orthonormal local bases in the mth unit cell. In the representation of these bases, the lattice Hamiltonian is an infinite-dimensional block-tridiagonal matrix: Here, as a convention, the region of the scatterers is chosen such that the hopping between the lead and the surface of a scatterer is the same as that inside this lead, e.g., H m L -1,m L = t in Fig. <ref type="figure">2</ref>(c), where t is the hopping inside the left lead. Except for the Hermiticity requirement H = H † , the lattice Hamiltonian is completely general. The (retarded) GF of the layered system is an infinite-dimensional matrix: G(E) ≡ (z -H) -1 , where z ≡ E + i0 + . The GF from the unit cell m 0 to the unit cell m is an M m × M m 0 matrix and corresponds to the (m,m 0 ) block of G(E), i.e., G m,m 0 (E) ≡ [(z -H) -1 ] m,m 0 . Hereafter we consider a fixed energy E or z ≡ E + i0 + and omit this argument for brevity.</p><formula xml:id="formula_1">H = ⎡ ⎢ ⎢ ⎢ ⎢ ⎢ ⎢ ⎢ ⎢ ⎢ ⎣ • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • H -2,-2 H -2,-1 0 0 0 • • • • • • H † -2,-1 H -1,-1 H -1,0 0 0 • • • • • • 0 H † -1,0 H 0,0 H 0,1 0 • • • • • • 0 0 H † 0,1 H 1,1 H 1,2 • • • • • • 0 0 0 H † 1,2 H 2,2 • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • ⎤ ⎥ ⎥ ⎥ ⎥ ⎥ ⎥ ⎥ ⎥ ⎥ ⎦ , (<label>1</label></formula><p>To highlight the distinguishing features of our approach and introduce relevant concepts, we first review the commonly used RGF method before presenting our idea.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>A. Recursive Green's function method</head><p>The idea of the RGF is to build up the entire system out of disconnected subsystems by the Dyson equation. Let us start from two disconnected subsystems A and B characterized by the Hamiltonian H (A) and H (B) , respectively. The (retarded) GFs of each subsystem are </p><formula xml:id="formula_2">G (A) ≡ (z -H (A) ) -1 and G (B) ≡ (z -H (B) ) -1 .</formula><formula xml:id="formula_3">G = G AA G AB G BA G BB (2)</formula><p>of the connected system in terms of the GFs of each subsystem <ref type="bibr" target="#b89">[90]</ref>:</p><formula xml:id="formula_4">G AA = (G (A) ) -1 -V ab G (B) bb V ba -1 , (<label>3a</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_5">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_6">G BB = (G (B) ) -1 -V ba G (A) aa V ab -1 ,<label>(3b)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_7">G BA = G (B) Bb V ba G aA ,<label>(3c)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_8">G AB = G (A) Aa V ab G bB ,<label>(3d)</label></formula><p>or vice versa:</p><formula xml:id="formula_9">G (A) = G AA -G Ab V ba (1 + G ab V ba ) -1 G aA ,<label>(4a)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_10">G (B) = G BB -G Ba V ab (1 + G ba V ab ) -1 G bB . (<label>4b</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_11">)</formula><p>Equation ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_4">3</ref>) is the key to building up the entire system out of disconnected subsystems, while Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_9">4</ref>) can be used to calculate the GF of each subsystem when the GF of the connected system is known (e.g., if the connected system is infinite and periodic <ref type="bibr" target="#b26">[27]</ref>). The first two equations of Eq. <ref type="bibr" target="#b2">(3)</ref> show that if we focus on one subsystem (say A), the presence of the other subsystem B amounts to a self-energy correction to the interface of A:</p><formula xml:id="formula_12">H (A) a,a → H (A) a,a + V ab G (B) bb V ba .</formula></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="1.">General procedures of RGF</head><p>In RGF, to calculate the conductance of the general layered system as described earlier [Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_1">1</ref>)], the system is first partitioned into the semi-infinite left lead L (unit cells m 0), the central region C (unit cells 1 m N ), and the semi-infinite right lead R (unit cells m N + 1). The entire central region C is regarded as a scatterer [see Fig. <ref type="figure">2</ref>(a) for an example], so the GF is</p><formula xml:id="formula_13">G = ⎡ ⎣ G LL G LC G LR G CL G CC G CR G RL G RC G RR ⎤ ⎦ .</formula><p>(</p><p>Let us use H (C)  </p><formula xml:id="formula_15">G CC = (z -H) -1 , (<label>6</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_16">)</formula><p>where H is the effective central region Hamiltonian: it equals H (C) in the interior of C, but differs from H (C) at the two surface unit cells:</p><formula xml:id="formula_17">H 1,1 = H 1,1 + (L) , (<label>7a</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_18">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_19">H N,N = H N,N + (R) , (<label>7b</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_20">)</formula><p>due to self-energy corrections from the left and right leads:</p><formula xml:id="formula_21">(L) = t † L G (L) s t L , (<label>8</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_22">) (R) = t R G (R) s t † R .<label>(9)</label></formula><p>Here G (L) s = [(z -H (L) ) -1 ] 0,0 is the GF of the left lead at the right surface, and</p><formula xml:id="formula_23">G (R) s = [(z -H (R) ) -1 ] N+1,N+1</formula><p>is the GF of the right lead at the left surface, so they are referred to as surface GFs in the literature. Finally, to compute the linear conductance, we need to set E = E F and use the Landauer-Buttiker formula <ref type="bibr" target="#b5">[6]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b6">[7]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b7">[8]</ref> σ = (e 2 /h)T (E F ), where <ref type="bibr" target="#b12">[13]</ref> T</p><formula xml:id="formula_24">(E F ) = Tr (R) G N,1 (L) (G N,1 ) † (10)</formula><p>and (α) ≡ i( (α) -H.c.). Note that Eq. ( <ref type="formula">10</ref>) only involves G N,1 , the (N,1) block of G CC . Instead of direct matrix inversion [see Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_15">6</ref>)], G N,1 can be computed by building up the central region layer by layer <ref type="bibr" target="#b1">[2]</ref> through Eq. (3). Let us use G (n) (n = 1,2, • • • ,N ) to denote the GF of the subsystem consisting of the unit cells m = 1,2, . . . ,n. The RGF starts from G (1) = (z -H 1,1 ) -1 , first uses the iteration</p><formula xml:id="formula_25">G (n) n,n = z -H n,n -H n,n-1 G (n-1) n-1,n-1 H n-1,n -1<label>(11)</label></formula><p>to obtain {G (n) n,n }, and then uses the iteration</p><formula xml:id="formula_26">G (n) 1,n = G (n-1) 1,n-1 H n-1,n G (n) n,n<label>(12)</label></formula><p>to obtain G 1,N = G (N) 1,N . The number of iterations and hence the time cost of the above recursive algorithm scales linearly with the length of the scattering region.</p><p>Equation <ref type="bibr" target="#b9">(10)</ref> gives the total transmission probability, i.e., the sum of the transmission probabilities of all channels. To identify the contributions from each individual transmission channel, it is necessary to use the GF to construct the transmission amplitude S (RL)  β,α from the αth traveling channel in the lead L to the βth traveling channel in the lead R through the Fisher-Lee relations <ref type="bibr" target="#b13">[14]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b14">[15]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b15">[16]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b16">[17]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b24">25,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b40">41,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">55]</ref> and then sum over all the traveling channels:</p><formula xml:id="formula_27">T (E F ) = αβ∈traveling S (RL) β,α 2 . (<label>13</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_28">)</formula><p>Alternatively, it is also possible to calculate the transmission amplitudes {S (RL) β,α } (and more generally the entire scattering matrix) by directly calculating the scattering of an incident traveling wave through the wave function mode matching approach <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">[52]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b52">[53]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b53">[54]</ref>. The equivalence between Eqs. ( <ref type="formula">10</ref>) and <ref type="bibr" target="#b12">(13)</ref>, which establishes a connection between the GF approach and the wave function mode matching approach, is well known for a single parabolic band <ref type="bibr" target="#b0">[1,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b1">2,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b13">[14]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b14">[15]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b15">[16]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b16">[17]</ref> . For a general lattice model, there was suspicion <ref type="bibr" target="#b76">[77]</ref> that Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_27">13</ref>) was incomplete since the GF in Eq. ( <ref type="formula">10</ref>) includes both traveling waves and evanescent waves, while Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_27">13</ref>) only includes the contributions from traveling waves. Later, a rigorous equivalence proof was provided by Khomyakov et al. <ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref> and others <ref type="bibr" target="#b24">[25]</ref>, but the presence of the evanescent states does suggest that the GF is not completely equivalent to the unitary scattering matrix.</p><p>There are still two remaining issues: the calculation of the self-energies (L,R) (or equivalently the surface GFs G (L,R) s ) and a proper definition of the scattering channels and the transmission amplitudes S (RL)  β,α .</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="2.">Self-energies: Recursive method and eigenmode method</head><p>The numerical algorithms for computing (L,R) or equivalently the surface GFs G (L,R) s can be classified into two groups: recursive methods and eigenmode methods (see Ref. <ref type="bibr" target="#b89">[90]</ref> for a review). The former calculates an approximate surface GF through some recursive relations, while the latter provides exact-within the numerical precision-closed-form solutions to the surface GF.</p><p>The idea of the recursive methods is to split the left lead into the surface unit cell m = 0 (subsystem A) and the remaining part (subsystem B); the Dyson equation [Eq. (3a)] gives the recursive relation</p><formula xml:id="formula_29">G (L) s = z -h L -t † L G (L) s t L -1 ⇔ (L) = t † L (z -h L -(L) ) -1 t L . (<label>14</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_30">)</formula><p>Similarly, by splitting the right lead into the surface unit cell m = N + 1 (subsystem A) and the remaining part (subsystem B), Eq. (3a) gives the recursive relation</p><formula xml:id="formula_31">G (R) s = z -h R -t R G (R) s t † R -1 ⇔ (R) = t R (z -h R -(R) ) -1 t † R . (<label>15</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_32">)</formula><p>Thus the surface GFs and self-energies can be obtained by simple or more efficient iteration techniques <ref type="bibr" target="#b31">[32,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b32">33]</ref>.</p><p>The eigenmode method has been derived independently several times <ref type="bibr" target="#b39">[40,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b40">41,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b45">46,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b51">52,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b52">53,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b76">77,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b90">91]</ref> and has been shown to be superior in accuracy and performance <ref type="bibr" target="#b39">[40]</ref> compared to the recursive methods. The central results are explicit expressions for the self-energies:</p><formula xml:id="formula_33">(L) = t † L (P (L) -) -1 , (<label>16a</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_34">) (R) = t R P (R) + , (<label>16b</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_35">)</formula><p>and surface GFs:</p><formula xml:id="formula_36">G (L) s = [z -h L -t † L (P (L) -) -1 ] -1 = (t L P (L) -) -1 ,<label>(17)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_37">G (R) s = (z -h R -t R P (R) + ) -1 = P (R) + (t † R ) -1 , (<label>18</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_38">)</formula><p>in terms of the (retarded) propagation matrices P (L,R)</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>±</head><p>(also referred to as Bloch matrices <ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref> or amplitude transfer matrices <ref type="bibr" target="#b89">[90]</ref> in the literature), which can be constructed from the (retarded) eigenmodes of each lead. Now we introduce the propagation matrices and eigenmodes in some detail, since they will play a central role in our GF approach. Let us consider a lead characterized by the unit cell Hamiltonian h and nearest-neighbor hopping matrix t = H m,m+1 . The wave propagation in this lead is governed by the uniform Schrödinger equation <ref type="bibr" target="#b18">(19)</ref> where z ≡ E + i0 + . Imposing the Bloch symmetry | (m) = e ikma | (a is the thickness of each unit cell) gives</p><formula xml:id="formula_39">-t † | (m -1) + (z -h)| (m) -t| (m + 1) = 0,</formula><formula xml:id="formula_40">z| = (e -ika t † + h + e ika t)| ≡ H(k)|<label>(20)</label></formula><p>for the eigenvector | . For an infinite lead, the wave function | (m) must remain finite at m → ±∞. This natural boundary condition dictates k to be real, so that Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_40">20</ref>) gives M real energy bands of the lead, where M is the number of basis states in each unit cell of this lead. For certain complex k's, the energies could still be real, which form the complex energy bands of the lead.</p><p>Conversely, given the energy E and without imposing any boundary conditions, Eqs. <ref type="bibr" target="#b18">(19)</ref> or <ref type="bibr" target="#b19">(20)</ref> can be solved to yield 2M(retarded) eigenmodes {k,| } (see Appendix A) <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">[52]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b52">[53]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b53">[54]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref>, where the wave vector k could be either real (i.e., traveling modes) or complex (i.e., evanescent modes). The eigenmodes are just the collection of eigenstates on the energy shell E in the real and complex energy bands of the lead. As a convention, each eigenvector | should be normalized to unity, but different eigenvectors are not necessarily orthogonal. For a traveling eigenmode with wave vector k and eigenvector | , its group velocity is</p><formula xml:id="formula_41">v = ∂ k |H(k)| = -2a Im |te ika | , (<label>21</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_42">)</formula><p>where | is the conjugate transpose of | , i.e., an Mcomponent row vector. Then the 2M eigenmodes are classified into M right-going ones and M left-going ones: the former consist of traveling modes with a positive group velocity and evanescent modes decaying exponentially to the right (i.e., Im k &gt; 0), while the latter consist of traveling modes with a negative group velocity and evanescent modes decaying exponentially to the left (i.e., Im k &lt; 0). For clarity, we denote the M right-going eigenmodes as {k +,α ,| +,α } and the M leftgoing eigenmodes as {k -,α ,| -,α }, where α = 1,2, . . . ,M. For every right-going evanescent mode (+,α) with wave vector k +,α , there is always a left-going evanescent mode (-,α) with wave vector k -,α = k * +,α <ref type="bibr" target="#b40">[41,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">55,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b91">92]</ref>.</p><p>The propagation matrix P s for left-going (s = -) or rightgoing (s = +) waves is constructed as <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">[52]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b52">[53]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b53">[54]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref> </p><formula xml:id="formula_43">P s ≡ U s ⎡ ⎢ ⎣ e ik s,1 a . . . e ik s,M a ⎤ ⎥ ⎦U -1 s , (<label>22</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_44">)</formula><p>where</p><formula xml:id="formula_45">U s ≡ [| s,1 , • • • ,| s,M ] (i.e., its αth column is | s,α</formula><p>). The propagation matrices are standard tools in the wave function mode matching approach <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">[52]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b52">[53]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b53">[54]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref> to describe wave propagation; e.g., a general right-going wave that obeys Eq. ( <ref type="formula">19</ref>) can be written as | (m) = P m + | (0) , while a general left-going wave obeying Eq. ( <ref type="formula">19</ref>) can be written as</p><formula xml:id="formula_46">| (m) = P m -| (0) .</formula></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="3.">Scattering channels and Fisher-Lee relations</head><p>Since the GF G(E) describes the scattering of both traveling and evanescent eigenmodes by the central region, while the unitary scattering matrix S(E) describes the scattering of traveling eigenmodes only, it is possible to construct S(E) in terms of G(E), i.e., the Fisher-Lee-type relations. Compared with the Caroli's expression [Eq. <ref type="bibr" target="#b9">(10)</ref>] that gives the total transmission probability, the Fisher-Lee relations further provide information about the scattering of each individual traveling eigenmode. For a general lattice model, different eigenmodes {| s,α } are not orthogonal; then for each lead, it is necessary to introduce 2M (retarded) dual vectors {|φ s,α } through <ref type="bibr" target="#b24">[25,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b40">41,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">55]</ref> ⎡</p><formula xml:id="formula_47">⎢ ⎣ φ s,1 | . . . φ s,M | ⎤ ⎥ ⎦ ≡ U -1 s , (<label>23</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_48">)</formula><p>where M is the number of bases in each unit cell of this lead.</p><p>In general, different left-going (right-going) eigenvectors are not orthogonal, so U s is not necessarily unitary and |φ s,α is not necessarily equal to | s,α , but we always have the orthonormalization and completeness relations</p><formula xml:id="formula_49">φ s,α | s,β = s,α |φ s,β = δ α,β , (<label>24</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_50">) α | s,α φ s,α | = α |φ s,α s,α | = I,<label>(25)</label></formula><p>which follow from U s U -1 s = U -1 s U s = I (I is the identity matrix). By inserting the completeness relation, any column vector | can be expanded as a linear combination of either the M left-going eigenvectors or the M right-going eigenvectors as | = α c s,α | s,α with c s,α = φ s,α | . In terms of the eigenmodes and their dual vectors, Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_43">22</ref>) can be written as</p><formula xml:id="formula_51">P s ≡ α e ik s,α a | s,α φ s,α |,<label>(26)</label></formula><p>which has a clear physical interpretation. For example, a general right-going wave is</p><formula xml:id="formula_52">| (m) = P m + | (0) = α e ik +,α ma | +,α φ +,α | (0) ;<label>(27)</label></formula><p>i.e., | (0) is first expanded as a linear combination of right-going eigenmodes</p><formula xml:id="formula_53">| (0) = α | +,α φ +,α | (0) and</formula><p>then each right-going eigenmode propagates as | +,α → e ik +,α ma | +,α . Now the scattering channel can be labeled by the eigenmodes, which could be either traveling or evanescent. The scattering matrix S(E) provides a complete description for the scattering from one traveling eigenmode into another traveling eigenmode. For a general lattice model, the Fisher-Lee relations allow us to construct the scattering matrix from the lattice GF; e.g., the transmission amplitude from the right-going eigenmode | (L) +,α of the left lead into the right-going eigenmode | (R) +,β of the right lead is <ref type="bibr" target="#b24">[25,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b40">41,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b51">52,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">55</ref>]</p><formula xml:id="formula_54">S (R,L) β,α α,β∈traveling = v (R) +,β /a R v (L) +,α /a L φ (R) +,β G N,1 (g (L) ) -1 (L) +,α ,<label>(28)</label></formula><p>while the transmission amplitude from the left-going eigenmode | (R) -,α of the right lead into the left-going eigenmode</p><formula xml:id="formula_55">| (L)</formula><p>-,β of the left lead is <ref type="bibr" target="#b24">[25,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b40">41,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b51">52,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">55</ref>]</p><formula xml:id="formula_56">S (L,R) β,α α,β∈traveling = v (L) -,β a L v (R) -,α a R φ (L) -,β G 1,N (g (R) ) -1 (R) -,α ,<label>(29)</label></formula><p>where a p and g (p) are, respectively, the unit cell thickness and free GF of the lead p [see Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_66">35</ref>)], and v </p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>B. Our GF approach: Key ideas</head><p>Let us assume that there is a local excitation at the unit cell m 0 , as described by an M m 0 -dimensional column vector | loc m 0 . This excitation generates a casual scattering wave | (m) that has an energy E and obeys the Schrödinger equation with a local source at m 0 :</p><formula xml:id="formula_57">-H m,m-1 | (m -1) + (z -H m,m )| (m) -H m,m+1 | (m + 1) = δ m,m 0 | loc m 0 . (<label>30</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_58">)</formula><p>The solution is given by</p><formula xml:id="formula_59">| (m) = G m,m 0 | loc m 0 ;<label>(31)</label></formula><p>e.g., for a unit excitation of the αth basis state, as described by | loc m 0 = [0, . . . ,1,0, . . . ,0] T (only the αth element is nonzero), Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_59">31</ref>) gives | (m) as the αth column of G m,m 0 . Equation <ref type="bibr" target="#b30">(31)</ref> shows that the GF can be immediately obtained once the scattering state is determined, e.g., based on physical considerations on how the local excitation evolves to the scattering state. For example, if the local excitation | loc m 0 occurs inside a lead, then it first generates an outgoing zeroth-order wave consisting of a left-going one at m m 0 and a right-going one at m m 0 . For an infinite lead, there are no scatterers, so this outgoing wave is the total scattering state [Fig. <ref type="figure">3(a)</ref>]. For a semi-infinite lead connected to a scatterer on its right [Fig. <ref type="figure">3(b)</ref>], the zeroth-order right-going wave will produce a first-order reflection wave, so the total scattering state in the lead is the sum of the zeroth-order and first-order waves. More generally, for a finite lead sandwiched FIG. <ref type="figure">3</ref>. Scattering state emanating from a local excitation at m 0 in an infinite lead (a), a semi-infinite lead connected to a scatterer on its right (b), and a finite lead sandwiched between two scatterers. The zeroth-order, first-order, and second-order partial waves are denoted by black, blue, and orange arrows, respectively. between two scatterers [Fig. <ref type="figure">3(c)</ref>], the right-going (left-going) zeroth-order wave will propagate to the right (left) scatterer and produce a first-order reflection wave, which in turn will propagate to the left (right) scatterer and then produce high-order reflection waves. The total scattering state would be the sum of all these waves.</p><p>In contrast to the commonly used RGF that treats the entire central region (regarded as a large scatterer) numerically [see Fig. <ref type="figure">2</ref>(a) for an example], our method need only regard each truly disordered region as a scatterer for numerical treatment, while all the periodic subregions [such as the middle lead in Fig. <ref type="figure">2(a)</ref>] inside the central region can be treated semianalytically by fully utilizing the translational invariance of these subregions. Physically, the wave propagation inside these periodic subregions leads to complicated multiple reflection between different scatterers, which is difficult to handle analytically in the standard RGF technique in which the GF is treated as a matrix. By contrast, in our approach, it is straightforward to perform analytically an infinite summation over all the multiple reflection waves, so that the time cost can be significantly reduced. This approach also provides a physically transparent expansion of the GF G(E) in terms of a generalized scattering matrix S(E), which can be regarded as a reverse of the well-known Fisher-Lee relations <ref type="bibr" target="#b13">[14]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b14">[15]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b15">[16]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b16">[17]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b24">25,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b40">41,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">55]</ref> (see Fig. <ref type="figure">1</ref>). In the next section, we will establish the procedures for calculating the GF within this framework in a physically transparent way.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>III. OUR GREEN'S FUNCTION APPROACH</head><p>Our GF approach essentially consists of two steps: generation of the zeroth-order outgoing partial wave by the local excitation and its propagation in the leads and scattering by the scatterers. The wave function mode matching approach <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">[52]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b52">[53]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b53">[54]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref> has developed useful tools to describe the latter process. Below we begin with an infinite lead, then we consider an infinite system containing a single scatterer. Finally, we give the analytical construction rule for the GF of a general layered system containing an arbitrary number of scatterers.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>A. Infinite lead</head><p>Suppose that the lead is characterized by the unit cell Hamiltonian h and hopping t. The scattering state | (m) emanating from a local excitation | loc m 0 is determined by the Schrödinger equation with a local source at m 0 :</p><formula xml:id="formula_60">-t † | (m -1) + (z -h)| (m) -t| (m + 1) = δ m,m 0 | loc m 0 . (<label>32</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_61">)</formula><p>In either the left region (m m 0 -1) or the right region (m m 0 + 1), the local source vanishes, so the general solution would be a linear combination of left-going and right-going eigenmodes with energy E. However, by causality considerations (due to the infinitesimal imaginary part of the energy z = E + i0 + ), the solution in the left (right) region should be a left-going (right-going) wave [see Fig. <ref type="figure">3(a)</ref>]:</p><formula xml:id="formula_62">| (m) | m m 0 -1 = (P -) m-m 0 | (m 0 ) , (<label>33</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_63">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_64">| (m) | m m 0 +1 = (P + ) m-m 0 | (m 0 ) . (<label>34</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_65">)</formula><p>Substituting into Eq. <ref type="bibr" target="#b31">(32)</ref> gives | (m 0 ) = g| loc m 0 , where</p><formula xml:id="formula_66">g ≡ (z -h -t † P -1 --tP + ) -1 (35a) = [t(P --P + )] -1 = [t † (P -1 + -P -1 -)] -1 . (<label>35b</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_67">)</formula><p>Here we have used the equality [55]</p><formula xml:id="formula_68">E -h = t † P -1 ± + tP ±<label>(36)</label></formula><p>in arriving at Eq. (35b). From the scattering wave function, we immediately identify the GF of an infinite lead as</p><formula xml:id="formula_69">g m,m 0 ≡ P m-m 0 + g (m m 0 ), P m-m 0 - g (m m 0 ).<label>(37)</label></formula><p>This recovers the previous result <ref type="bibr" target="#b40">[41,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">55]</ref> obtained by directly solving the equations of motion of the GF. For convenience, hereafter we call g m,m 0 the free GF of the lead since it describes the generation of the zeroth-order outgoing wave | (m) = g m,m 0 | loc m 0 from a local excitation inside this lead.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>B. Single scatterer</head><p>Let us consider a scatterer C connected to two semi-infinite leads L and R [Fig. <ref type="figure">4(a)</ref>]. The left (right) surface of the scatterer is m L (m R ). The unit cell Hamiltonian and hopping inside the left (right) lead are h L and t L (h R and t R ).</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="1.">Local excitation inside the scatterer</head><p>The zeroth-order outgoing wave | (m) emanating from a local excitation | loc m 0 at m 0 ∈ C obeys Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_57">30</ref> m m R , i.e., inside the scatterer. Inside the left lead, | (m) obeys</p><formula xml:id="formula_70">-t † L | (m -1) + (z -h L )| (m) -t L | (m + 1) = 0 (38)</formula><p>with m m L -1. Inside the right lead, | (m) obeys</p><formula xml:id="formula_71">-t † R | (m -1) + (z -h R )| (m) -t R | (m + 1) = 0 (<label>39</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_72">)</formula><p>with m m R + 1. By causality, the solution in the left (right) lead is a left-going (right-going) wave [see Fig. <ref type="figure">4</ref>(a)]:</p><formula xml:id="formula_73">| (m) | m∈L = (P (L) -) m-m L | (m L ) , (<label>40</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_74">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_75">| (m) | m∈R = (P (R) + ) m-m R | (m R ) , (<label>41</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_76">)</formula><p>where</p><formula xml:id="formula_77">P (p)</formula><p>± are propagation matrices of lead p [see Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_43">22</ref>)]. <ref type="formula" target="#formula_57">30</ref>) gives a closed set of equations for | (m) inside the scatterer. The solution is</p><formula xml:id="formula_78">Substituting | (m L -1) = (P (L) -) -1 | (m L ) and | (m R + 1) = P (R) + | (m R ) into Eq. (</formula><formula xml:id="formula_79">| (m) | m∈C = G m,m 0 | loc m 0 ,<label>(42)</label></formula><p>where</p><formula xml:id="formula_80">G ≡ (z -H) -1<label>(43)</label></formula><p>and H is the effective Hamiltonian for the scatterer: it is equal to the scatterer part of the system Hamiltonian H, except for the two surface unit cells:</p><formula xml:id="formula_81">H m L ,m L = H m L ,m L + t † L (P (L) -) -1 , (<label>44a</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_82">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_83">H m R ,m R = H m R ,m R + t R P (R) + . (<label>44b</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_84">)</formula><p>Since G converts a local excitation inside the scatterer into a scattering state inside the scatterer, we call it the conversion matrix of the scatterer. Comparing Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_80">43</ref>) and (44) to Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_15">6</ref>), <ref type="bibr" target="#b6">(7)</ref>, and ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_33">16</ref>), we see that G is just the scatterer part of the GF. Actually, from the scattering wave function, we immediately identify the GF:</p><formula xml:id="formula_85">G m∈C,m 0 ∈C = G m,m 0 , (<label>45a</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_86">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_87">G m∈L,m 0 ∈S = (P (L) -) m-m L G m L ,m 0 , (<label>45b</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_88">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_89">G m∈R,m 0 ∈S = (P (R) + ) m-m R G m R ,m 0 . (45c)</formula><p>Equation (45b) shows that the local excitation first evolves to an outgoing wave G m L ,m 0 | loc m 0 at the left surface of the scatterer, and then propagates to the unit cell m as (P (L) -) m-m L G m L ,m 0 | loc m 0 . Equation (45c) has a similar physical interpretation.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="2.">Local excitation in the lead</head><p>As shown in Fig. <ref type="figure">4</ref>(b), for m 0 ∈ L, the local excitation first generates a zeroth-order outgoing wave in the left lead:</p><formula xml:id="formula_90">| (0) (m) = g (L)</formula><p>m,m 0 | loc m 0 , where g</p><formula xml:id="formula_91">(p)</formula><p>m,m 0 is the free GF of the lead p [Eq. <ref type="bibr" target="#b36">(37)</ref>]. Next the right-going partial wave reaches the left surface of C and evolves into a scattering state | (m) . For m 0 ∈ R, the local excitation first generates a zeroth-order outgoing wave in the right lead:</p><formula xml:id="formula_92">| (0) (m) = g (R)</formula><p>m,m 0 | loc m 0 . Next the left-going partial wave reaches the right surface of C and evolves to a scattering state | (m) . For either case, the total scattering state | (m) emanating from the local excitation is the sum of the unscattered zeroth-order partial wave and the scattering state | (m) . The central issue is to determine the scattering state emanating from a known incident wave, in a way similar to the wave function mode matching approach to mesoscopic quantum transport <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">[52]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b52">[53]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b53">[54]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref>.</p><p>First we consider the scattering state | (m) emanating from a right-going incident wave | in (m) in the left lead. The key observation is that for arbitrary m 1 m L , the local excitation</p><formula xml:id="formula_93">| loc m 1 ≡ (g (L) ) -1 | in (m 1 ) generates a right- going partial wave | ˜ (m) | m m 1 = (P (L) + ) m-m 1 | in (m 1 ) that is equal to | in (m) | m m 1 .</formula><p>Therefore, in the region m m 1 , the scattering state emanating from | in (m) is the same as the scattering state emanating from this local excitation (see Appendix B for a rigorous proof). Taking m 1 = m L immediately gives</p><formula xml:id="formula_94">| (m) | m∈C = G m,m L (g (L) ) -1 | in (m L ) ;<label>(46)</label></formula><p>i.e., first the incident wave amplitude </p><formula xml:id="formula_95">| in (m L ) is converted back to a local excitation | loc m L ≡ (g (L) ) -1 | in (m L )</formula><formula xml:id="formula_96">| m∈L = (P (L) -) m-m L | r (m L ) , where | r (m L ) = | (m L ) -| in (m L ) = G m L ,m L (g (L) ) -1 -I | in (m L ) . (<label>47</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_97">)</formula><p>Inside the right lead, | (m) is the right-going transmission wave:</p><formula xml:id="formula_98">| (m) | m∈R = (P (R) + ) m-m R | (m R ) , where | (m R ) = G m R ,m L (g (L) ) -1 | in (m L ) . (<label>48</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_99">)</formula><p>Similarly, we can derive the scattering state | (m) emanating from a left-going incident wave | in (m) in the right lead. Inside the scatterer, the scattering state is </p><formula xml:id="formula_100">| (m) | m∈S = G m,m R (g (R) ) -1 | in (m R ) , (<label>49</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_101">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_102">as if it emanated from a local excitation | loc m R ≡ (g (R ) -1 | in (m R )</formula><formula xml:id="formula_103">| m∈R = (P (R) + ) m-m R | r (m R ) , where | r (m R ) = | (m R ) -| in (m R ) = G m R ,m R (g (R) ) -1 -I | in (m R ) . (<label>50</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_104">)</formula><p>Inside the left lead, | (m) is the left-going transmission wave:</p><formula xml:id="formula_105">| (m) = (P (L) -) m-m L | (m L ) , where | (m L ) = G m L ,m R (g (R) ) -1 | in (m R ) . (<label>51</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_106">)</formula><p>Using the above results, the scattering state emanating from the zeroth-order right-going partial wave in the left lead is given by Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_94">46</ref>)- <ref type="bibr" target="#b47">(48)</ref> with | in (m L ) ≡ | (0) (m L ) . This allows us to identify the GF:</p><formula xml:id="formula_107">G m∈C,m 0 ∈L = G m,m L (g (L) ) -1 g (L)</formula><p>m L ,m 0 , (52a)</p><formula xml:id="formula_108">G m∈R,m 0 ∈L = (P (R) + ) m-m R G m R ,m L (g (L) ) -1 g (L) m L ,m 0 , (52b) G m∈L,m 0 ∈L = g (L) m,m 0 + (P (L) -) m-m L G m L ,m L (g (L) ) -1 -I g (L) m L ,m 0 . (<label>52c</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_109">)</formula><p>These expressions have clear physical interpretations; e.g., Eq. (52a) shows that the local excitation | loc m 0 ∈L first evolves to a right-going partial wave and propagates rightward to the left surface of the scatterer as g (L) m L ,m 0 | loc m 0 ∈L . There it is converted back to a local excitation by (g (L) ) -1 , and finally the conversion matrix of the scatterer G m,m L further converts it to the scattering state inside the scatterer. As another example, Eq. (52c) shows that the total scattering wave inside the left lead is the sum of the zeroth-order partial wave g (L)  m,m 0 | loc m 0 and the reflection partial wave: first the local excitation | loc m 0 ∈L evolves to a zeroth-order partial wave and then propagates rightwards to the left surface of the scatterer as g (L)  m L ,m 0 | loc m 0 ∈L , then G m L ,m L (g (L) ) -1 -I converts it to the reflection wave. Finally, (P (L) -) m-m L propagates this reflection wave leftward to m.</p><p>Similarly, the scattering state emanating from the zerothorder left-going partial wave in the right lead is given by Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_100">49</ref>)- <ref type="bibr" target="#b50">(51)</ref> with | in (m R ) ≡ | (0) (m R ) . This allows us to identify the GF:</p><formula xml:id="formula_110">G m∈C,m 0 ∈R = G m,m R (g (R) ) -1 g (R) m R ,m 0 , (<label>53a</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_111">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_112">G m∈L,m 0 ∈R = (P (L) -) m-m L G m L ,m R (g (R) ) -1 g (R) m R ,m 0 , (<label>53b</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_113">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_114">G m∈R,m 0 ∈R = g (R) m,m 0 + (P (R) + ) m-m R G m R ,m R (g (R) ) -1 -I g (R) m R ,m 0 . (<label>53c</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_115">)</formula><p>These can be interpreted in a similar way to Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_85">45</ref>) and <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">(52)</ref>.</p><p>The above results cover previous results as special cases. For example, by directly solving the equation of motion, Sanvito et al. <ref type="bibr" target="#b40">[41]</ref> and Krstić et al. <ref type="bibr" target="#b76">[77]</ref> obtain the GF of an infinite lead [Eq. <ref type="bibr" target="#b36">(37)</ref>] and a semi-infinite lead consisting of the unit cells m 0 (m 0) [Eq. (C2)], which can be regarded as a single-unit-cell scatterer at m = 0 connected to a semi-infinite left (right) lead. Khomyakov et al. <ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref> further obtained the GF across a single scatterer [Eq. (52b)]. A sharp interface between a semi-infinite left lead and a semi-infinite right lead can also be regarded as a single-unit-cell scatterer connected to two semi-infinite leads. For reference, the explicit expressions of the GFs for these simple cases are given in Appendix C.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>C. Multiple scatterers</head><p>A general layered system containing an arbitrary number of scatterers can be regarded as a composite scatterer connected to one or two semi-infinite leads, e.g., a scatterer B connected to a finite lead L and a semi-infinite lead R can be regarded as a composite scatterer C = (A + B) connected to one semiinfinite right lead [Fig. <ref type="figure" target="#fig_5">5(a)</ref>], while two scatterers sandwiched between three leads can be regarded a composite scatterer  <ref type="formula" target="#formula_85">45</ref>), <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">(52)</ref>, and ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_110">53</ref>) to obtain the GF of the entire system once the conversion matrix of the composite scatterer is known. In the RGF method, the conversion matrix (which coincides with the GF of the infinite system within the composite scatterer) is calculated by a numerical iteration algorithm that builds up the composite scatterer slice by slice; thus the time cost increases linearly with the total length of the composite scatterer. Here the physical transparency of our approach allows us to treat the multiple reflection between different scatterers analytically, so that the conversion matrix of a composite scatterer can be obtained by combining the conversion matrices of the constituent scatterers analytically with a significantly reduced time cost. The basic step is the combination of the conversion matrices G (A) and G (B) of two scatterers A and B into the conversion matrix G of a composite scatterer C ≡ (A + B).</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="1.">Combining conversion matrices</head><p>As shown in Fig. <ref type="figure" target="#fig_5">5</ref> </p><formula xml:id="formula_116">| (m) | m∈A = G (A) m,a R (g (M) ) -1 | -(a R ) . (<label>54</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_117">)</formula><p>Inside the scatterer B, | (m) is equal to the scattering state emanating from the total incident wave</p><formula xml:id="formula_118">| + (b L ) on B [cf.</formula><p>Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_94">46</ref>)]:</p><formula xml:id="formula_119">| (m) | m∈B = G (B) m,b L (g (M) ) -1 | + (b L ) . (<label>55</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_120">)</formula><p>Therefore, the scattering state inside C is completely determined by | + (b L ) and | -(a R ) . For brevity, we introduce the reflection matrices</p><formula xml:id="formula_121">R B ≡ G (B) b L ,b L (g (M) ) -1 -I,<label>(56)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_122">R A ≡ G (A) a R ,a R (g (M) ) -1 -I. (<label>57</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_123">)</formula><p>The former (latter) converts a right-going (left-going) incident wave on the left (right) surface of B (A) to a left-going (right-going) reflection wave. To describe the multiple reflections between A and B, we introduce the following renormalized propagation matrices that incorporate multiple reflections:</p><formula xml:id="formula_124">P b L ←a R ≡ [1 -(P (M) + ) m R A (P (M) -) -m R B ] -1 (P (M) + ) m , (<label>58</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_125">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_126">P a R ←b L ≡ [1 -(P (M) -) -m R B (P (M) + ) m R A ] -1 (P (M) -) -m , (<label>59</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_127">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_128">P a R ←a R ≡ (P (M) -) -m R B P b L ←a R = P a R ←b L R B (P (M) + ) m , (<label>60</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_129">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_130">P b L ←b L ≡ (P (M) + ) m R A P a R ←b L = P b L ←a R R A (P (M) -) -m ,<label>(61)</label></formula><p>where m ≡ b La R is the distance between A and B. For example, the renormalized propagation matrix P b L ←a R from a R to b L is the sum of the free propagation term (P (M) + ) m , the propagation term with two reflections (P (M) + ) m R A (P (M) -) -m R B (P (M) + ) m , and so on. Using the above notations, when | in (m) is a right-going incident wave on B, we have</p><formula xml:id="formula_131">| + (b L ) = 1 + P b L ←b L R B | in (b L ) , (<label>62</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_132">) | -(a R ) = P a R ←b L R B | in (b L ) . (<label>63</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_133">)</formula><p>When | in (m) is a left-going incident wave on A, we have</p><formula xml:id="formula_134">| + (b L ) = P b L ←a R R A | in (a R ) ,<label>(64)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_135">| -(a R ) = 1 + P a R ←a R R A | in (a R ) . (<label>65</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_136">)</formula><p>Using the above results together with</p><formula xml:id="formula_137">| (m) | m∈C = G m,m 0 | loc m 0 , we identify G m∈B,m 0 ∈A = G (B) m,b L (g (M) ) -1 P b L ←a R G (A) a R ,m 0 , (66a) G m∈A,m 0 ∈B = G (A) m,a R (g (M) ) -1 P a R ←b L G (B) b L ,m 0 , (66b) G m∈A,m 0 ∈A = G (A) m,m 0 + G (A) m,a R (g (M) ) -1 P a R ←a R G (A) a R ,m 0 , (66c) G m∈B,m 0 ∈B = G (B) m,m 0 + G (B) m,b L (g (M) ) -1 P b L ←b L G (B) b L ,m 0 , (66d) G m∈M,m 0 ∈A = (P (M) + ) m-a R 1 + R A P a R ←a R + (P (M) -) m-b L R B P b L ←a R G (A) a R ,m 0 , (66e) G m∈A,m 0 ∈M = G (A) m,a R (g (M) ) -1 1 + P a R ←a R R A g (M) a R ,m 0 + P a R ←b L R B g (M) b L ,m 0 , (66f) G m∈M,m 0 ∈B = (P (M) -) m-b L 1 + R B P b L ←b L + (P (M) + ) m-a R R A P a R ←b L G (B) b L ,m 0 , (<label>66g</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_138">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_139">G m∈B,m 0 ∈M = G (B) m,b L (g (M) ) -1 1 + P b L ←b L R B g (M) b L ,m 0 + P b L ←a R R A g (M) a R ,m 0 , (<label>66h</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_140">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_141">G m∈M,m 0 ∈M = g (M) m,m 0 + (P (M) + ) m-a R R A P a R ←b L R B g (M) b L ,m 0 + (P (M) -) m-b L R B P b L ←a R R A g (M)</formula><p>a R ,m 0</p><formula xml:id="formula_142">+ (P (M) -) m-b L R B + R B P b L ←b L R B g (M) b L ,m 0 + (P (M) + ) m-a R R A + R A P a R ←a R R A g (M) a R ,m 0 . (<label>66i</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_143">)</formula><p>These equations can be interpreted in a physically transparent way. For example, Eq. (66a) shows that the local excitation at m 0 ∈ A evolves to the scattering wave at m ∈ B through the following steps: first it is converted by G (A) a R ,m 0 to a zeroth-order partial wave at a R , next it undergoes renormalized propagation from a R to b L , and finally it is converted back to a local excitation and then to the scattering wave at m ∈ B.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="2.">Analytical construction rule for multiple scatterers</head><p>By repeatedly using Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_137">66</ref>), the conversion matrix of a composite scatterer can be obtained analytically as functions of the conversion matrices of the constituent scatterers. In particular, the four surface elements of the conversion matrix of the composite scatterer can be immediately obtained from those of the constituent scatterers:</p><formula xml:id="formula_144">G b R ,a L = G (B) b R ,b L (g (M) ) -1 P b L ←a R G (A) a R ,a L , (67a) G a L ,b R = G (A) a L ,a R (g (M) ) -1 P a R ←b L G (B) b L ,b R , (67b) G a L ,a L = G (A) a L ,a L + G (A) a L ,a R (g (M) ) -1 P a R ←a R G (A) a R ,a L , (67c) G b R ,b R = G (B) b R ,b R + G (B) b R ,b L (g (M) ) -1 P b L ←b L G (B) b L ,b R , (<label>67d</label></formula><p>) while the latter can be calculated through recursive techniques [Eqs. <ref type="bibr" target="#b10">(11)</ref> and <ref type="bibr" target="#b11">(12)</ref>].</p><p>For example, let us consider an infinite layered system with eight scatterers S 1 ,S 2 , . . . ,S 8 and calculate its GF G m,m 0 . For simplicity we assume that m 0 and m are both inside the leads or at the surfaces of the scatterers (see Fig. <ref type="figure">6</ref>), so that G m,m 0 is just the (m,m 0 ) element of the conversion matrix G of the composite scatterer (S 1 + S 2 + • • • + S 8 ), i.e., G m,m 0 = G m,m 0 , and G m,m 0 is completely determined by the surface elements of G (S 1 ) , . . . ,G (S 8 ) , which are readily obtained through recursive techniques. First, we use Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_144">67</ref>) to calculate the surface elements of G (A) , G (B 1 ) , and G (B 2 ) for the three composite scatterers A ≡ (S 1 + S 2 + S 3 ), B 1 ≡ (S 4 + S 5 + S 6 ), and B 2 ≡ (S 7 + S 8 ). Next we regard (B 1 + B 2 ) as a composite scatterer B and calculate G (B) m,b L (b L is the left surface of B) from Eq. (66e). Now the entire system contains two scatterers A and B; thus G m,m 0 can be obtained from Eq. (66h).</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>IV. INVERSE OF FISHER-LEE RELATION</head><p>In the previous section, we have developed a physically transparent and numerically efficient way to calculate the GF of a general layered system. There the GF is expressed as a matrix, i.e., in terms of the propagation matrices P ± and conversion matrix g of the leads and the conversion matrices G of the scatterers. In this section, we give further physical insight into our GF approach by expressing the GF analytically in terms of a generalized scattering matrix, which describes the scattering of both traveling states and evanescent states. This could be regarded as the inverse of the well-known Fisher-Lee relations <ref type="bibr" target="#b13">[14]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b14">[15]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b15">[16]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b16">[17]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b24">25,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b40">41,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">55]</ref> (see Fig. <ref type="figure">1</ref>). The key is to express the conversion matrix G in terms of a generalized scattering matrix.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>A. Generalized scattering matrix</head><p>Let us consider an infinite system consisting of a single scatterer (with the left surface at m L and the right surface at m R ) connected to two semi-infinite leads L and R (see Fig. <ref type="figure">4</ref>). Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_51">26</ref>) for the propagation matrix, we obtain</p><formula xml:id="formula_145">| (m) | m m R = β e ik (R) +,β (m-m R )a R (R) +,β S (RL) β,α ,<label>(68)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_146">| (m) | m m L = | in (m) + β e ik (L) -,β (m-m L )a L (L) -,β S (LL) β,α ,<label>(69)</label></formula><p>where</p><formula xml:id="formula_147">S (RL) β,α ≡ φ (R) +,β G m R ,m L (g (L) ) -1 (L) +,α<label>(70)</label></formula><p>is a generalized transmission amplitude from | (L) +,α at the left surface of the scatterer into | (R)</p><p>+,β at the right surface of the scatterer, and</p><formula xml:id="formula_148">S (LL) β,α ≡ φ (L) -,β G m L ,m L (g (L) ) -1 -I (L) +,α<label>(71)</label></formula><p>is a generalized reflection amplitude from</p><formula xml:id="formula_149">| (L) +,α into | (L) -,β</formula><p>at the left surface of the scatterer. Similarly, for a left-</p><formula xml:id="formula_150">going incident wave | in (m) = e ik (R) -,α (m-m R )a R | (R)</formula><p>-,α in the right lead, the resulting scattering state | (m) follows from Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_100">49</ref>)- <ref type="bibr" target="#b50">(51)</ref> as</p><formula xml:id="formula_151">| (m) | m m L = β e ik (L) -,β (m-m L )a L (L) -,β S (LR) β,α ,<label>(72)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_152">| (m) | m m R = | in (m) + β e ik (R) +,β (m-m R )a R S (RR) β,α (R) +,β ,<label>(73)</label></formula><p>where</p><formula xml:id="formula_153">S (LR) β,α ≡ φ (L) -,β G m L ,m R (g (R) ) -1 (R) -,α<label>(74)</label></formula><p>is a generalized transmission amplitude from | (R) -,α at the right surface of the scatterer into | (L)</p><p>-,β at the left surface of the scatterer, and</p><formula xml:id="formula_154">S (RR) β,α ≡ φ (R) +,β G m R ,m R (g (R) ) -1 -I (R) -,α<label>(75)</label></formula><p>is a generalized reflection amplitude from</p><formula xml:id="formula_155">| (R) -,α into | (R) +,β</formula><p>at the right surface of the scatterer. Equations ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_147">70</ref>)-( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_154">75</ref>) define a generalized scattering matrix S(E) and express it in terms of the surface elements of the conversion matrix. They were first derived in the wave function mode matching approach <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">[52]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b52">[53]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b53">[54]</ref> and its connection to the GF approach was established later <ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref>. They are valid for both traveling modes and evanescent modes. In our GF approach, these expressions have clear physical meanings. Taking S (RL)   β,α as an example, G m R ,m L (g (L) ) -1 converts the incident eigenmode | (L)</p><p>+,α at the left surface of the scatterer back to a local excitation and then to the scattering wave at the right surface of the scatterer. Then the dual vector φ (R) +,β | projects the scattering wave onto the eigenmode | (R)</p><formula xml:id="formula_156">+,β</formula><p>[see Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_49">24</ref>) and ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_50">25</ref>)]. The transmission and reflection amplitudes of the unitary scattering matrix connecting two traveling eigenmodes are obtained by normalizing with respect to the current <ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref>:</p><formula xml:id="formula_157">S (q,p) β,α α,β∈traveling = v (q) s out ,β a q v (p)</formula><p>s in ,α /q p S (q,p)</p><formula xml:id="formula_158">β,α ;<label>(76)</label></formula><p>where s in = s out = + for (q,p) = (R,L); s in = s out =for (q,p) = (L,R); s in = +, s out =for (q,p) = (L,L); and s in = -, s out = + for (q,p) = (R,R), thus Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_147">70</ref>) and ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_153">74</ref>) lead to Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_54">28</ref>) and ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_56">29</ref>), respectively.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>B. Inverse of Fisher-Lee relations</head><p>The inverse of Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_147">70</ref>)-( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_154">75</ref>) gives the surface elements of G(E) in terms of the generalized scattering matrix S(E):</p><formula xml:id="formula_159">G m R ,m L = α ⎛ ⎝ β S (RL) β,α (R) +,β ⎞ ⎠ φ (L)</formula><p>+,α g (L) , (77a)</p><formula xml:id="formula_160">G m L ,m R = α ⎛ ⎝ β S (LR) β,α (L) -,β ⎞ ⎠ φ (R) -,α g (R) , (<label>77b</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_161">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_162">G m L ,m L = α ⎛ ⎝ (L) +,α + β S (LL) β,α (L) -,β ⎞ ⎠ φ (L) +,α g (L) , (<label>77c</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_163">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_164">G m R ,m R = α ⎛ ⎝ (R) -,α + β S (RR) β,α (R) +,β ⎞ ⎠ φ (R) -,α g (R) . (<label>77d</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_165">)</formula><p>These expressions have very clear physical interpretations. For example, Eq. (77a) shows that a local excitation | loc m L at the left surface of the scatterer evolves to the scattering wave at the right surface of the scatterer through two steps.</p><p>First, it evolves to a partial wave g (L) | loc m L , then it is expanded into linear combinations of right-going eigenmodes α | (L) +,α φ (L) +,α |g (L) | loc m L and each eigenmode transmits across the scatterer to its right surface as (L)</p><formula xml:id="formula_166">+,α → β S (RL) β,α (R) +,β .<label>(78)</label></formula><p>Similarly, Eq. (77c) shows that a local excitation at the left surface of the scatterer first evolves to a partial wave g (L) | loc m L , then it is expanded as α | (L) +,α φ (L) +,α |g (L) | loc m L and each eigenmode evolves to a scattering wave:</p><formula xml:id="formula_167">(L) +,α → (L) +,α + β (L) -,β S (LL) β,α , (<label>79</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_168">)</formula><p>which consists of the incident wave and the reflection wave.</p><p>Next, we can express other blocks of the GF, i.e., Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_85">45</ref>)-( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_110">53</ref>) with m,m 0 inside the leads, in terms of the generalized scattering matrix:</p><formula xml:id="formula_169">G m∈R,m 0 ∈L = α ⎛ ⎝ β e ik (R) +,β (m-m R )a (R) +,β S (RL) β,α ⎞ ⎠ × e ik (L) +,α (m L -m 0 )a φ (L) +,α g (L) , (<label>80a</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_170">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_171">G m∈L,m 0 ∈R = α ⎛ ⎝ β e ik (L) -,β (m-m L )a (L) -,β S (LR) β,α ⎞ ⎠ × e ik (R) -,α (m R -m 0 )a φ (R) -,α g (R) , (80b) G m∈L,m 0 ∈L = g (L) m,m 0 + α ⎛ ⎝ β e ik (L) -,β (m-m L )a (L) -,β S (LL) β,α ⎞ ⎠ × e ik (L) +,α (m L -m 0 )a φ (L) +,α g (L) , (80c) G m∈R,m 0 ∈R = g (R) m,m 0 + α ⎛ ⎝ β e ik (R) +,β (m-m R )a (R) +,β S (RR) β,α ⎞ ⎠ × e ik (R) -,α (m R -m 0 )a φ (R) -,α g (R) . (<label>80d</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_172">)</formula><p>The above expressions have clear physical meanings. For example, Eq. (80a) shows that a local excitation | loc m 0 in the left lead first evolves to a partial wave g (L) | loc m 0 and then propagates freely to the left surface of the scatterer as α e ik (L)</p><formula xml:id="formula_173">+,α (m L -m 0 )a | (L) +,α φ (L) +,α |g (L) | loc m 0 . Finally each eigenmode | (L)</formula><p>+,α evolves to a transmission wave:</p><formula xml:id="formula_174">(L) +,α → β e ik (R) +,β (m-m R )a R (R) +,β S (RL) β,α . (<label>81</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_175">)</formula><p>As another example, Eq. (80c) shows that G m∈L,m 0 ∈L is the sum of the free GF g (L) m,m 0 and the reflection wave contribution, which emerges as follows: the local excitation | loc m 0 in the left lead first evolves to a partial wave g (L) | loc m 0 and then propagates freely to the left surface of the scatterer as</p><formula xml:id="formula_176">α e ik (L) +,α (m L -m 0 )a | (L) +,α φ (L) +,α |g (L) | loc m 0 .</formula><p>Finally, each mode evolves to a reflection wave:</p><formula xml:id="formula_177">(L) +,α → β e ik (L) -,β (m-m L )a L (L) -,β S (LL) β,α .<label>(82)</label></formula><p>Equation ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_169">80</ref>) not only allows us to construct the GF from the generalized scattering matrix, but also reveals the contribution of each individual scattering channels to the GF.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>C. On-shell spectral expansion</head><p>The Fisher-Lee relations <ref type="bibr" target="#b13">[14]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b14">[15]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b15">[16]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b16">[17]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b24">25,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b40">41,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">55]</ref> and its inverse [Eq. <ref type="bibr" target="#b79">(80)</ref>] provide a complete one-to-one correspondence between the lattice GF approach and the wave function mode matching approach <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">[52]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b52">[53]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b53">[54]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref> to mesoscopic quantum transport (see Fig. <ref type="figure">1</ref>). Next we show that we can construct the GF G(E) analytically in terms of a few scattering states on the energy shell E. Since the latter can be readily obtained from standard textbook technique and approximation methods (such as the WKB approximation), this provides a convenient way to obtain the GF.</p><p>Let us introduce 2M advanced eigenmodes { ks,α ,| ˜ s,α } of each lead <ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref>, <ref type="bibr" target="#b82">(83)</ref> and their dual vectors:</p><formula xml:id="formula_178">ks,α ≡ k s,α , | ˜ s,α ≡ | s,α (α ∈ evanescent ), ks,α ≡ k -s,α , | ˜ s,α ≡ | -s,α (α ∈ traveling),</formula><formula xml:id="formula_179">⎡ ⎢ ⎣ φs,1 | . . . φs,M | ⎤ ⎥ ⎦ ≡ Ũ-1 s , (<label>84</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_180">)</formula><p>where  <ref type="formula" target="#formula_49">24</ref>) and ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_50">25</ref>)]. Using <ref type="bibr" target="#b54">[55]</ref> g</p><formula xml:id="formula_181">-1 = α | φ-,α iv +,α a φ +,α | = α | φ+,α -iv -,α a φ -,α |,<label>(85)</label></formula><p>and the completeness relations Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_50">25</ref>), we obtain</p><formula xml:id="formula_182">g = α | +,α a iv +,α ˜ -,α | = α | -,α a -iv -,α ˜ +,α |<label>(86)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_183">-→ α | +,α a iv +,α +,α | = α | -,α a -iv -,α -,α |,<label>(87)</label></formula><p>where the second line holds when all the eigenmodes are traveling modes. Here a is the unit cell spacing of the lead and v s,α is the generalized group velocity of the eigenmode (s,α): for a traveling mode, it equals the group velocity [Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_41">21</ref>)]; for an evanescent mode, it is defined as</p><formula xml:id="formula_184">v +,α = v * -,α = -ia -,α |(e ik -,α a ) * t † -e ik +,α a t| +,α . (<label>88</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_185">)</formula><p>Note that for an evanescent (traveling) mode, v s,α depends (does not depend) on the choice of the phases of the eigenvectors {| s,α }.</p><p>To express the GF in terms of on-shell scattering states, we introduce the eigenmode wave functions</p><formula xml:id="formula_186">| +,α (m) ≡ e ik +,α (m-m 0 )a | +,α (m m 0 ), 0 ( m &lt; m 0 ),<label>(89a)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_187">| -,α (m) ≡ 0 ( m m 0 ), e ik -,α (m-m 0 )a | -,α (m &lt; m 0 ), (<label>89b</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_188">)</formula><p>for the lead in which m 0 locates. Note that so-defined | s,α (m) depends on m 0 , which is regarded as fixed and hence omitted for brevity. If there were no scatterers, then G m,m 0 would coincide with the free GF of this lead [Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_69">37</ref>)], which can be written as</p><formula xml:id="formula_189">g m,m 0 = a α | +,α (m) ˜ -,α | iv +,α + | -,α (m) ˜ +,α | -iv -,α . (<label>90</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_190">)</formula><p>Due to the presence of scatterers, each eigenmode | s,α (m) evolves to a corresponding scattering state | s,α (m) , so replacing | s,α (m) in Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_189">90</ref>) with | s,α (m) gives the GF:</p><formula xml:id="formula_191">G m,m 0 = a α | +,α (m) ˜ -,α | iv +,α + | -,α (m) ˜ +,α | -iv -,α . (<label>91</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_192">)</formula><p>Since the total scattering state | s,α (m) can be decomposed into the sum of the incident wave | s,α (m) (which vanishes outside the lead in which m 0 locates) and the outgoing scattering wave</p><formula xml:id="formula_193">| (out) s,α (m) ≡ | s,α (m) -| s,α (m) , Eq. (<label>91</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_194">)</formula><p>can also be written as</p><formula xml:id="formula_195">G m,m 0 = g m,m 0 + a α (out) +,α (m) ˜ -,α | iv +,α + (out) -,α (m) ˜ +,α | -iv -,α , (<label>92</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_196">)</formula><p>where g m,m 0 is nonzero only for m in the same lead as m 0 . Equations ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_191">91</ref>) or <ref type="bibr" target="#b91">(92)</ref> shows that the GF G m,m 0 (E) is essentially certain scattering states {| s,α (m) } (on the energy shell E) that obey outgoing boundary conditions; i.e., they emanate from the on-shell eigenmodes | s,α (m) of the lead in which the local excitation occurs. Compared with the standard spectral expansion in classic textbook on quantum mechanics <ref type="bibr" target="#b77">[78]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b78">[79]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b79">[80]</ref> that expresses the GF in terms of all the eigenstates (both on-shell eigenstates and off-shell ones) of the system, Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_191">91</ref>) or ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_195">92</ref>) deepens our physical understanding about the GF and allows analytical reconstruction of the GF from a few scattering states of the system.</p><p>As an example, let us consider an infinite system containing a single scatterer (Fig. <ref type="figure">4</ref>). For m 0 in the left lead, the left-going eigenmode | (L) -,α (m) is not scattered, so | (L,out) -,α (m) = 0, while the right-going eigenmode | (L) +,α (m) produces an outgoing scattering wave (L,out)</p><formula xml:id="formula_197">+,α (m) m∈L = ⎛ ⎝ β e ik (L) -,β (m-m L )a (L) -,β S (LL) β,α ⎞ ⎠ × e ik (L) +,α (m L -m 0 )a ,<label>(93)</label></formula><p>(L,out)</p><formula xml:id="formula_198">+,α (m) m∈R = ⎛ ⎝ β e ik (R) +,β (m-m R )a (R) +,β S (RL) β,α ⎞ ⎠ × e ik (L) +,α (m L -m 0 )a .<label>(94)</label></formula><p>Substituting into Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_195">92</ref>) gives Eqs. (80a) and (80c). Similarly, for m 0 in the right lead, the right-going eigenmode</p><formula xml:id="formula_199">| (R) +,α (m) is not scattered, so | (R,out) +,α (m) = 0, while the left-going eigenmode | (R) -,α (m) produces the outgoing wave (R,out) -,α (m) m∈L = ⎛ ⎝ β e ik (L) -,β (m-m L )a (L) -,β S (LR) β,α ⎞ ⎠ × e ik (R) -,α (m R -m 0 ) a , (<label>95</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_200">) (R,out) -,α (m) m∈R = ⎛ ⎝ β e ik (R) +,β (m-m R )a (R) +,β S (RR) β,α ⎞ ⎠ × e ik (R) -,α (m R -m 0 )a . (<label>96</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_201">)</formula><p>Substituting them into Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_195">92</ref>) gives Eqs. (80b) and (80d).</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>V. EXAMPLE AND APPLICATIONS</head><p>Here we first exemplify our general results in a 1D chain and then apply the formalism to graphene p-n junctions described by the tight-binding model.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>A. Simple example: 1D chain</head><p>We consider a 1D chain characterized by one basis state in each unit cell, the unit cell Hamiltonian h = ε 0 , and the nearest-neighbor hopping t = -t &lt; 0. For a given wave vector k, Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_40">20</ref>) can be solved to yield the energy E(k) = ε 0 -2t cos(ka), which is real in two cases: (1) k ∈ R;</p><p>(2) k = iκ or k = π/a + iκ with κ ∈ R. The former gives the real energy band, while the latter gives the complex energy bands. For specificity we consider the energy E ∈ [ε 0 -2t,ε 0 + 2t], so there is one right-going traveling eigenmode k + = k with group velocity v = 2at sin(ka) &gt; 0 and one leftgoing traveling eigenmode k -= -k with group velocity -v, where k is the positive solution to E = E(k). The eigenvectors of the eigenmodes and dual vectors are ± = φ ± = 1. The propagation matrices are P ± = e ±ika , the conversion matrix of the lead is</p><formula xml:id="formula_202">g = 1 2it sin(ka) = 1 iv/a , (<label>97</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_203">)</formula><p>and the free GF of the lead is</p><formula xml:id="formula_204">g m,m 0 = e ik|m-m 0 |a iv/a . (<label>98</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_205">)</formula><p>When the on-site energy of the unit cell m 1 of the infinite 1D chain is replaced by ε 0 + δ, the unit cell m 1 becomes a scatterer characterized the conversion matrix</p><formula xml:id="formula_206">G = 1 iv/a -δ ,<label>(99)</label></formula><p>or equivalently the transmission amplitude T = Gg -1 = (iv/a)/(iv/aδ) and reflection amplitude R = Gg -1 -1 = δ/(iv/aδ). The GFs of the entire system are given by Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_85">45</ref>), <ref type="bibr" target="#b51">(52)</ref>, and <ref type="bibr" target="#b52">(53)</ref> as</p><formula xml:id="formula_207">G m m 1 ,m 0 m 1 = e ik(m-m 1 )a T e ik(m 1 -m 0 )a iv/a = T e ik(m-m 0 )a iv/a ,<label>(100)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_208">G m m 1 ,m 0 m 1 = e -ik(m-m 1 )a T e -ik(m 1 -m 0 )a iv/a = T e -ik(m-m 0 )a iv/a ,<label>(101)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_209">G m m 1 ,m 0 m 1 = e ika|m-m 0 | iv/a + e -ik(m-m 1 )a Re ik(m 1 -m 0 )a iv/a ,<label>(102)</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_210">G m m 1 ,m 0 m 1 = e ika|m-m 0 | iv/a + e ik(m-m 1 )a Re -ik(m 1 -m 0 )a iv/a . (<label>103</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_211">)</formula><p>The above results are also consistent with Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_169">80</ref>). Finally, when the on-site energies of unit cell m 1 and unit cell m 2 (&gt;m 1 ) are both replaced by ε 0 + δ, then each unit cell becomes a scatterer characterized by the conversion matrix in Eq. <ref type="bibr" target="#b98">(99)</ref>. The conversion matrix G (C) of the composite scatterer (m 1 + m 2 ) is given by Eq. <ref type="bibr" target="#b65">(66)</ref>. In particular, the surface elements are obtained from Eq. <ref type="bibr" target="#b66">(67)</ref> as</p><formula xml:id="formula_212">G (C) m 2 m 1 = G (C) m 1 m 2 = e ik(m 2 -m 1 )a T (1 -e 2ik(m 2 -m 1 )a R 2 ) -1 T iv/a , (<label>104</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_213">)</formula><formula xml:id="formula_214">G (C) m 1 m 1 = G (C) m 2 m 2 = G + e 2ik(m 2 -m 1 )a T R(1 -e 2ik(m 2 -m 1 )a R 2 ) -1 T iv/a ,<label>(105)</label></formula><p>from which we can obtain the generalized transmission amplitude across the composite scatterer as</p><formula xml:id="formula_215">T (C) ≡ G (C) m 2 ,m 1 g -1 = T (1 -e 2ik(m 2 -m 1 )a R 2 ) -1 e ik(m 2 -m 1 )a T , (<label>106</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_216">)</formula><p>and the generalized reflection amplitude as</p><formula xml:id="formula_217">R (C) ≡ G (C) m 1 m 1 g -1 -1 = R + e 2ik(m 2 -m 1 )a T R(1 -e 2ik(m 2 -m 1 )a R 2 ) -1 T . (107)</formula></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>B. Chiral tunneling and anomalous focusing in graphene p-n junction</head><p>Graphene is a single layer of carbon atoms in a honeycomb lattice that hosts massless Dirac fermions <ref type="bibr" target="#b92">[93]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b93">[94]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b94">[95]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b95">[96]</ref>. One of the unique properties of electrons in graphene is chiral tunneling <ref type="bibr" target="#b80">[81]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b81">[82]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b82">[83]</ref>: an electron normally incident on a potential barrier will always be perfectly transmitted, independently of its kinetic energy and the height and width of the potential barrier (for oblique incidence, the transverse momentum serves as a gap-opening mass term, so the transmission is not perfect, and bound states may be created by a 1D potential well <ref type="bibr" target="#b102">[103,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b103">104]</ref>). In recent years, the chiral tunneling in graphene p-n junctions has attracted a lot of attention (see Ref. <ref type="bibr" target="#b96">[97]</ref> for a review). Another interesting phenomenon for electrons in graphene p-n junctions is the anomalous focusing due to negative refraction, which was initially proposed by Veselago for electromagnetic waves <ref type="bibr" target="#b97">[98]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b98">[99]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b99">[100]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b100">[101]</ref>: a spatially diverging pencil of rays is focused to a spatially converging one during the transition from a medium with positive refractive index across a sharp interface into a negative index medium. In 2007, Cheianov et al. <ref type="bibr" target="#b83">[84]</ref> proposed that ballistic graphene p-n junctions can also exhibit negative refraction and hence focus the electron flow: in the electron-doped n (hole-doped p) region, the carrier group velocity is parallel (antiparallel) to its momentum, in analogy to light propagation in a positive (negative) refractive index medium. Ever since then, there have been a lot of works on the negative refraction in graphene (see Refs. <ref type="bibr" target="#b84">[85,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b85">86]</ref> for examples) and on the surface of topological insulators <ref type="bibr" target="#b101">[102]</ref>. Recently, the Veselago lens effect in graphene was observed experimentally <ref type="bibr" target="#b86">[87,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b87">88]</ref>.</p><p>On the theoretical side, most of the previous studies focus on traveling states and are based on the low-energy continuous model, whose validity is limited to the vicinity of the Dirac points. A very recent work <ref type="bibr" target="#b104">[105]</ref>, based on the tight-binding model, calculates numerically the propagation of a wave packet in a large but finite graphene flake to approximate the Klein tunneling and caustics of electron waves. Here we apply our general GF formalism to study the chiral tunneling in an infinite graphene p-n junction and pay special attention to the evanescent eigenmode. Our approach provides a clear physical picture and allows us to calculate the GF over long distances, so we further perform both analytical analysis and numerical simulations of dual-probe STM measurements. Our results demonstrate the possibility of observing the spatially resolved interference pattern caused by the negative refraction in graphene p-n junctions and further reveal a few interesting features, such as the distance-independent conductance and its quadratic dependence on the carrier concentration, as opposed to the linear dependence in uniform graphene.</p><p>We consider a graphene p-n junction with an interface that can be either sharp or smooth, as shown in Fig. <ref type="figure" target="#fig_9">7</ref>(a). In the tight-binding model, the interface could align along different crystalline directions. To provide the simplest description, a tilted coordinate system is usually necessary: we choose one primitive vector a 2 (defined as the y axis) of the Bravais lattice of uniform graphene to be parallel to the interface, and choose the x axis of our tilted coordinate system to be parallel to the other primitive vector a 1 ; i.e., the two nonorthogonal unit vectors of the tilted coordinate are e x ≡ a 1 /|a 1 | and e y ≡ a 2 /|a 2 |, as shown in Figs. 7(b)-7(d) for the interface along the zigzag direction, armchair direction, and a more general direction. This choice of the primitive vectors and the tilted coordinate system ensures that the lattice Hamiltonian is invariant upon translation by |a 2 | along the y axis, so that the original 2D lattice model can be reduced to a 1D lattice model.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="1.">Reduction from 2D to 1D</head><p>For specificity, we assume that the interface is along the zigzag direction [Fig. <ref type="figure" target="#fig_9">7(c</ref> </p><formula xml:id="formula_218">G R m 2 n 2 ,R m 1 n 1 ,E = 1 N y k y e ik y (n 2 -n 1 )a G m 2 ,m 1 (E,k y ),<label>(111)</label></formula><p>where G(R m 2 n 2 ,R m 1 n 1 ,E) and G m 2 ,m 1 (E,k y ) are both 2 × 2 matrices. Below we consider fixed E and k y and apply our general results to calculate the GF G m 2 ,m 1 of the 1D lattice, with E and k y omitted for brevity.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="2.">Green's function of 1D lattice</head><p>In the 1D lattice, the hopping is uniform:</p><formula xml:id="formula_219">H (1D) m,m+1 = H (1D) m+1,m † = t = 0 0 t 0 . (<label>112</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_220">)</formula><p>The unit cell Hamiltonian H (1D) m,m = V m + h 0 is the sum of the unit cell Hamiltonian of pristine graphene,</p><formula xml:id="formula_221">h 0 = 0 t(1 + e ik y a ) t(1 + e -ik y a ) 0 , (<label>113</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_222">)</formula><p>and the p-n junction potential V m . The entire infinite system consists of a single scatterer (m L m m R ) connected to two semi-infinite leads L and R [cf. Fig. <ref type="figure" target="#fig_9">7</ref>(a)], whose GFs can be constructed from the conversion and propagation matrices of the leads and the conversion matrix G of the p-n interface (see Sec. III and Sec. IV). The remaining issue is to calculate the eigenmodes of each lead, as characterized by the hopping t and the unit cell Hamiltonian h = V + h 0 , where V = V L (left lead) or V R (right lead). Given a complex wave vector k, we can solve the eigenvalue problem Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_40">20</ref>) and obtain the energy bands of the lead as V ± E 0 (k), where E 0 (k) ≡ t f (k,k y )f (-k,k y ) FIG. <ref type="figure">8</ref>. Real energy band (black lines) and complex energy bands (orange lines) of pristine graphene at a fixed k y ≈ 0.14 × 2π/a. and f (k,k y ) ≡ 1 + e ik y a + e -ika . Here E 0 (k) is real in two cases: <ref type="bibr" target="#b0">(1)</ref> </p><formula xml:id="formula_223">k + k y /2 = κ; (2) k + k y /2 = iκ or π/a + iκ,</formula><p>where κ ∈ R. The former gives the real energy bands, while the latter gives the complex energy bands, as shown in Fig. <ref type="figure">8</ref>. Conversely, given the energy E, we can solve Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_40">20</ref>) and obtain a right-going eigenmode k + ,| + and a left-going eigenmode k -,| -, where k ± are the two solutions to |E -V | = E 0 (k) or equivalently the two intersection points of E -V with the real and complex energy bands of pristine graphene. When E -V lies in the range of the real energy bands (dashed black line in Fig. <ref type="figure">8</ref>), the wave vectors k ± are both real and both eigenmodes are traveling modes. When E -V lies outside the range of the real energy bands (dashed gray line in Fig. <ref type="figure">8</ref>), the wave vectors k + = k * -are complex and both eigenmodes are evanescent. A more convenient method to obtain the eigenmodes is to define λ ≡ e ika and rewrite Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_40">20</ref>) as</p><formula xml:id="formula_224">λ 2 bt + λ[|b| 2 + t 2 -(E -V ) 2 ] + tb * = 0 (114)</formula><p>with b ≡ t(1 + e ik y a ), so that λ ± = e ik ± a are obtained as the two solutions to this quadratic equation for λ. In addition to the two normal eigenmodes, there are also a pair of ideally evanescent eigenmodes, including a right-going one λ +,0 = e ik +,0 a = 0, | +,0 = [1,0] T and a left-going one λ -,0 = e ik -,0 a = ∞, | -,0 = [0,1] T (see Appendix A). The ideally evanescent eigenmodes do not propagate, so they do not directly contribute to the GF, but their existence does influence the generalized transmission and reflection amplitudes of the normal eigenmodes.</p><p>Using the eigenmodes, we can calculate the conversion matrix G of the p-n interface using Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_80">43</ref>) and then obtain the generalized transmission and reflection amplitudes S (LL) , S (RL) , S (LR) , and S (RR) of the normal eigenmode from Eqs. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_147">70</ref>)- <ref type="bibr" target="#b74">(75)</ref>. For m = m 0 , the free GF of the left lead is essentially the sum of the left-going eigenmode | (L) -(m) and the right-going eigenmode | (L)  + (m) [cf. Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_186">89</ref>) for their definitions]:</p><formula xml:id="formula_225">g (L) m,m 0 = a iv (L) + | (L) + (m) ˜ (L) -| + a -iv (L) - | (L) -(m) ˜ (L) + |. (<label>115</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_226">)</formula><p>Due to the p-n interface, the eigenmode | (L) + (m) produces a reflection wave in the left lead and a transmission wave in the right lead:</p><formula xml:id="formula_227">| (L,out) + (m) = e ik (L) -(m-m L )a | (L) -S (LL) e ik (L) + (m L -m 0 )a (m ∈ L), e ik (R) + (m-m R )a | (R) + S (RL) e ik (L) + (m L -m 0 )a (m ∈ R),<label>(116)</label></formula><p>so the GF from the left lead to the right lead is essentially the transmission wave:</p><formula xml:id="formula_228">G m∈R,m 0 ∈L = a iv (L) + | (L,out) + (m) ˜ (L) -|,<label>(117)</label></formula><p>while the GF inside the left lead is essentially the sum of the incident eigenmode | (L) ± (m) and the reflection wave:</p><formula xml:id="formula_229">G m∈L,m 0 ∈L = g (L) m,m 0 + a iv (L) + | (L,out) + (m) ˜ (L) -|. (<label>118</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_230">)</formula></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="3.">Green's function of 2D graphene p-n junction: Anomalous focusing</head><p>Compared with the standard RGF method, the advantages of our GF method lie in its physical transparency and numerical efficiency. Here we demonstrate the first point by using our method to provide a clear physical picture of the anomalous focusing effect <ref type="bibr" target="#b83">[84]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b84">[85]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b85">[86]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b86">[87]</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b87">[88]</ref> across the graphene p-n junction described by the tight-binding model. For this purpose, we first obtain the GF of the 2D graphene p-n junction from the 1D GFs by a Fourier transform [Eq. ( <ref type="formula" target="#formula_218">111</ref>)]. In particular, the GF from the unit cell (m 1 ,n 1 ) in the n region to the unit cell (m 2 ,n 2 ) in the p region,</p><formula xml:id="formula_231">G R m 2 n 2 ,R m 1 n 1 ,E = dk y 2π (L,tran) + R m 2 n 2 a iv (L) + ˜ (L) -|,<label>(119)</label></formula><p>is essentially the sum of all transmission wave functions</p><formula xml:id="formula_232">(L,tran) + R m 2 n 2 ≡ e ik (R) + •(R m 2 n 2 -R m R ,0 ) | (R) + S (RL) e ik (L) + •(R m L ,0 -R m 1 n 1 ) , (<label>120</label></formula><formula xml:id="formula_233">)</formula><p>which emanates from the incident eigenmode</p><formula xml:id="formula_234">| (L) + (R m,n ) = e ik (L) + •(R m,n -R m 1 n 1 ) | (L)</formula><p>+ through three steps: propagation to the left interface R m L ,0 of the junction with wave vector k (L)  + , transmission across the interface, and propagation from R m R ,0 to R m 2 n 2 with wave vector k (R)  + . Here k (L) ± (k (R) ± ) are the wave vectors of the normal eigenmodes in the left (right) region, i.e., in the tilted coordinate [Fig. <ref type="figure" target="#fig_9">7</ref> </p><formula xml:id="formula_235">(E F ) ∝ |G(R m 2 n 2 ,R m 1 n 1 ,E F )| 2 .</formula><p>Therefore, Eq. (119) directly connects the transmission wave function to the experimentally measurable conductance and hence provides a clear physical picture for observing the anomalous focusing in dual-probe STM measurements, and further reveals some interesting effects.</p><p>Let us consider a sharp, symmetric interface at m L = m R = 0 and V R = -V L = V 0 &gt; 0. In this case, the transmission wave simplifies to</p><formula xml:id="formula_236">(L,tran) + R m 2 n 2 ≡ e i(k (R) + •R m 2 n 2 -k (L) + •R m 1 n 1 ) | (R)</formula><p>+ S (RL) . (121)</p><p>Here k (R) + , k (L) + , | (R) + , and S (RL) all depend on k y weakly. The strongest dependence on k y comes from the phase factor e i(k (R)</p><formula xml:id="formula_237">+ •R m 2 n 2 -k (L) + •R m 1 n 1 )</formula><p>, which usually oscillates rapidly as a function of k y when R m 2 n 2 and R m 1 n 1 are far away. However, when the energy of the incident electron lies midway in between the Dirac point of the n region and the Dirac point of the p region (i.e., E = E F = 0), in the Cartesian coordinate system spanned by the orthogonal unit vectors e X and e Y [see Fig. <ref type="figure" target="#fig_9">7(b)</ref>], the electron-hole symmetry of graphene dictates that the Fermi wave vector k (L)  + of the right-going eigenmode in the n region and the Fermi wave vector k (R)  + of the right-going eigenmode in the p region to have the same component along the p-n interface (i.e., k (L)  + • e Y = k (R) + • e Y ), but opposite components perpendicular to the p-n interface (i.e., k (L)  + • e X = -k (R) + • e X ). Therefore, when R m 1 n 1 and R m 2 n 2 are mirror symmetric about the p-n interface, the rapidly oscillating phase factor equals unity for all k y . In this case, all the transmitted waves have nearly the same phase factor for all k y , so they contribute constructively to the GF. This corresponds to electrons flowing out of an electron source at R m 1 n 1 being focused to R m 2 n 2 , i.e., the anomalous focusing <ref type="bibr" target="#b83">[84]</ref>. According to the Landauer-Büttiker formula, the constructive enhancement of the GF could be detected as an enhanced conductance in dual-probe STM measurements.</p><p>In addition to locally enhancing the GF, the constructive interference of all the transmission waves also gives rise to two interesting behaviors. First, the phase factor e i(k (R)</p><formula xml:id="formula_238">+ •R m 2 n 2 -k (L) + •R m 1 n 1 )</formula><p>and hence the transmission wave and the GF remain invariant when R m 2 n 2 and R m 1 n 1 are moved equally but in opposite directions perpendicular to the p-n interface. This would give rise to distance-independent conductance. Second, since each transmission wave contributes constructively to the GF, we have G(R m 2 n 2 ,R m 1 n 1 ,E F ) ∝ density of states on the Fermi surface ∝V 0 ∝ carrier concentration. Thus the locally enhanced conductance should increase quadratically with increasing doping level V 0 (or equivalently the carrier concentration), in contrast to the linear dependence in uniform graphene <ref type="bibr" target="#b70">[71]</ref>. These points will be verified in our subsequent numerical simulations of the dual-probe STM measurements, which provide a useful tool, with high spatial resolution, to measure such local transport properties and detect possible zero-energy bound states of the Dirac fermions caused by suitable 2D potential well <ref type="bibr" target="#b105">[106,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b106">107]</ref>.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="4.">Comparison of the standard RGF and our GF approach</head><p>Compared with the standard RGF that treats the entire central region numerically [see Fig. <ref type="figure">2</ref>(a) for an example], an important advantage of our approach is that it fully utilizes the translational invariance of all the periodic subregions [even if they lie inside the central region, such as the middle lead in Fig. <ref type="figure">2(a)</ref>] to treat these subregions semianalytically, so that only the truly disordered subregions need numerical treatment. Therefore, our GF approach is more efficient if the central region contains periodic subregions; otherwise the two approaches are equally efficient. Here we calculate G(R 2 ,R 1 ,E) across a sharp graphene p-n junction using these two methods to demonstrate their equivalence and highlight the numerical efficiency of our approach. In the calculation, R 1 is fixed at a randomly chosen A sublattice site in the n region; R 2 is swept over all the B sublattice sites along the x axis from the n region to the p region. The range of the sweep is from 0.25 μm on the left of R 1 to 0.75 μm on the right of R 1 . For the RGF method, the central region (infinite along the p-n interface) is the smallest region that encloses R 1 , R 2 , and the p-n interface. For our GF method, the scatterer region (infinite along the p-n interface) consists of one slice at the p-n interface. The numerical results from the two approaches always agree with each other up to the machine accuracy. The time cost, however, differs by two orders of magnitude: with 90 Intel cores, the time cost of the standard RGF approach varies from 260 s to 540 s, depending on the position of R 1 relative to the p-n interface, while the time cost of our approach is always less than 3 s. Similar speedup is expected in long multilayer structures with sharp interfaces, such as quantum wells, superlattices, or sharp p-n-p junctions.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head n="5.">Numerical examples</head><p>In the following (main text and all the figures), we always use the C-C bond length of graphene a C-C = 0.142 nm as the unit of length and the nearest-neighbor hopping amplitude t = 3 eV as the unit of energy. For specificity, we focus on symmetric graphene p-n junctions with V R = -V L = V 0 &gt; 0. Unless explicitly specified, we always take a typical doping level V 0 = 0.2 and set the energy E = E F = 0, so we denote G(R 2 ,R 1 ,E) by G(R 2 ,R 1 ) for brevity.</p><p>As shown in Fig. <ref type="figure">9</ref>, at V 0 = 0.2, the tunneling of a right-going traveling eigenmode reproduces the well-known 9. Transmission and reflection of a right-going eigenmode of energy E = 0 incident from the n region of a sharp (solid lines and dotted lines) or 5-nm-wide smooth (dashed lines), symmetric (i.e., -V L = V R = V 0 ) graphene p-n junction. For V 0 = 0.2, the range of k y in which the eigenmode is traveling is marked by the double arrow. For V 0 = 0.02, the range of k y in which the eigenmode is traveling is much narrower.</p><p>results from the continuum model <ref type="bibr" target="#b96">[97]</ref>, such as the perfect transmission at normal incidence. For the evanescent eigenmode in a sharp p-n junction, however, |S (RL) | 2 shows a peak, indicating enhanced tunneling of certain evanescent states. When the Fermi level is tuned closer to the Dirac point, i.e., for V 0 = 0.02, this enhanced tunneling becomes more pronounced and may be observed by dual-probe STM measurements.</p><p>Next we visualize the contributions from different scattering channels to the GF and their interference. For a smooth junction, the spatial map of the GF [Fig. <ref type="figure" target="#fig_13">10</ref> Finally we simulate dual-probe STM measurements <ref type="bibr" target="#b70">[71,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b107">108]</ref> over the graphene p-n junction at zero temperature. Following Refs. <ref type="bibr" target="#b70">[71,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b107">108]</ref>, we assume that each probe couples to a single carbon site for simplicity, so the Landauer-Büttiker formula <ref type="bibr" target="#b0">[1]</ref> gives the interprobe conductance as σ (R 2 ,R 1 ) = (2e 2 /h)T 12 (E F ) = 1 2 | Ḡ(R 2 ,R 1 ,E F )| 2 , where Ḡ(R 2 ,R 1 ,E F ) is the GF incorporating the self-energy corrections from the STM probes and 1,2 are coupling constants between the STM probes and the graphene. Usually, 1,2 have a sensitive exponential dependence on the distance between the STM probe and the graphene sample, but their specific values do not affect the shape of the signal. Therefore, following Ref. <ref type="bibr" target="#b107">[108]</ref>, we always rescale the maximum of T 12 to unity. In Fig. <ref type="figure" target="#fig_14">11</ref>, the real-space conductance map shows a pronounced focusing due to negative refraction <ref type="bibr" target="#b83">[84]</ref>. Other observable electron optics features include the high transparency of the junction near normal incidence, i.e., chiral tunneling <ref type="bibr" target="#b81">[82]</ref>, and the interference pattern between the incident and reflection waves. Recently, negative refraction in graphene p-n junctions was observed <ref type="bibr" target="#b86">[87]</ref>, but the measurement via macroscopic contacts only gives a spatially averaged result. Here our simulation shows that dual-probe STM measurements can further provide spatially resolved interference pattern; i.e., dual-probe STM could be an ideal experimental technique for studying local transport and quantum interference phenomenon. Now we demonstrate numerically some interesting features of the dual-probe STM measurements in graphene p-n junctions [see the physical analysis following Eq. ( <ref type="formula">121</ref>)]. First, when the two probes are mirror symmetric about the junction interface, T 12 is nearly independent of the interprobe distance [Fig. <ref type="figure">12(a)</ref>], in contrast to the 1/R decay in uniform graphene <ref type="bibr" target="#b70">[71]</ref>. For a sharp junction, this behavior can be attributed to the anomalous focusing <ref type="bibr" target="#b83">[84]</ref>. However, the existence of the same behavior for a smooth junction interface indicates that it has a different physical origin, i.e., the cancellation of the propagation phases due to the matching of the electron Fermi surfaces in the n region and the hole Fermi surface in the p region <ref type="bibr" target="#b108">[109]</ref>. The distance-independent response could change qualitatively the spatial scaling of many physical quantities, such as the Friedel oscillation induced by an impurity and the carrier-mediated RKKY interaction between two localized magnetic moments. Second, the conductance across a sharp junction scales quadratically with the junction potential: T 12 ∝ V 2 0 [red line in Fig. <ref type="figure">12</ref> qualitatively from the linear scaling T 12 ∝ V 0 of uniform graphene <ref type="bibr" target="#b70">[71]</ref>. When the junction becomes smooth [inset of Fig. <ref type="figure">12(b)</ref>], the quadratic dependence still persists for small V 0 (electron's Fermi wavelength junction width), but recovers the linear scaling behavior in uniform graphene for large V 0 . This can be attributed to the gradual destruction of the anomalous focusing when the junction width becomes larger than the Fermi wavelength <ref type="bibr" target="#b82">[83]</ref>.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>VI. CONCLUSIONS</head><p>We have presented a numerically efficient and physically transparent formalism to calculate and understand the Green's function (GF) of a general layered structure. In contrast to the commonly used recursive GF method that directly calculates the GF through the Dyson equations, our approach converts the calculation of the GF to the generation and subsequent propagation of a scattering wave function emanating from a local excitation. This viewpoint provides analytical expressions of the GF in terms of a generalized scattering matrix. This identifies the contributions of individual scattering channels to the GF and hence allows this information to be extracted quantitatively from dual-probe STM experiments. We further derive an analytical rule to construct the GF of a general layered system, which could significantly reduce the computational time cost and enable quantum transport calculations for large samples. Application of this formalism to simulate the two-dimensional conductance map of a realistic graphene p-n junction demonstrates the possibility of observing the spatial interference caused by negative refraction and further reveals a few interesting features, such as the distance-independent conductance and its quadratic dependence on the carrier concentration, as opposed to the linear dependence in uniform graphene. In addition to conventional mesoscopic quantum transport, it would be interesting to apply our GF approach to the investigation of other electron interference phenomena, such as the carrier-mediated RKKY interaction between local magnetic moments, the impurity-induced Friedel oscillation, and using dual-probe STM measurements to detect possible zero-energy bound states in graphene caused by suitable 2D potentials <ref type="bibr" target="#b105">[106,</ref><ref type="bibr" target="#b106">107]</ref>.</p></div><figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_0"><head/><label/><figDesc>Next we connect the interface (denoted by a) of A and the interface (denoted by b) of B by local couplings V ab and V ba . Thus the Dyson equation gives the GF</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_1"><head/><label/><figDesc>is the group velocity [see Eq. (21)] of the traveling eigenmode | (p) s,α in the lead p.</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_2"><head/><label/><figDesc>FIG.<ref type="bibr" target="#b3">4</ref>. Scattering state emanating from a local excitation inside a scatterer (a) or a lead (b). The black arrows denote the zeroth-order partial wave and the blue arrows denote the first-order partial wave due to scattering.</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_3"><head/><label/><figDesc>, then the conversion matrix G of the scatterer further converts it to the total scattering state | (m) | m∈C according to Eq. (42). Inside the left lead, | (m) is the sum of the right-going incident wave and a left-going reflection partial wave | r (m)</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_4"><head/><label/><figDesc>at the right surface of the scatterer [cf. Eq. (42)]. Inside the right lead, | (m) is the sum of the left-going incident wave and a right-going reflection partial wave | r (m)</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_5"><head>FIG. 5 .</head><label>5</label><figDesc>FIG. 5. (a) A scatterer B connected to a finite left lead L and a semi-infinite right lead R can be regarded as a composite scatterer C connected to one semi-infinite right lead R. (b) Two scatterers sandwiched between three leads L,M,R can be regarded as a composite scatterer C connected to two semi-infinite leads L and R.</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_6"><head/><label/><figDesc>(b), the left and right surfaces of the scatterer A (B) are a L and a R (b L and b R ) and the three leads sandwiching the scatterers are the semi-infinite left lead L, the middle lead M, and the semi-infinite right lead R. For a local excitation | loc m 0 at m 0 ∈ C, the total scattering state inside C is | (m) | m∈C = G m,m 0 | loc m 0 , which allows us to identify G once the total scattering state has been obtained. For m 0 ∈ A, the local excitation first produces a zeroth-order partial wave in A and M. Next the right-going partial wave in M undergoes multiple reflections between B and A and finally evolves to a scattering state. For m 0 ∈ B, the local excitation first produces a zeroth-order partial wave inside B and M. Next the left-going partial wave in M undergoes multiple reflections and finally evolves to a scattering state. For m 0 ∈ M, the local excitation first produces a zeroth-order outgoing partial wave in M. Next the left-and right-going partial waves each undergo multiple reflections and evolve to a scattering state. For each case, the total scattering state emanating from the local excitation is the sum of the unscattered zeroth-order partial wave and the scattering state(s) emanating from the scattered zerothorder partial wave. Therefore, the key issue is to calculate the scattering state | (m) emanating from a right-or left-going incident wave | in (m) in the middle lead through multiple reflections between A and B. In the middle lead, | (m) is the sum of the rightgoing part | + (m) = (P (M) + ) m-b L | + (b L ) and the left-going part | -(m) = (P (M) -) m-a R | -(a R ) . Inside the scatterer A, | (m) is equal to the scattering state emanating from the total incident wave | -(a R ) on A [cf. Eq. (49)]:</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_7"><head/><label/><figDesc>FIG. 6. Green's function G m,m 0 of an infinite system containing eight scatterers, where m 0 and m are both inside the leads or at the surfaces of the scatterers.</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_8"><head/><label/><figDesc>Ũs ≡ [| ˜ s,1 , . . . ,| ˜ s,M ]. The advanced eigenvectors {| ˜ s,α } and dual vectors {| φs,α } obey exactly the same orthonormal and completeness relations as their retarded counterpart [Eqs. (</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_9"><head>FIG. 7 .</head><label>7</label><figDesc>FIG. 7. (a) Sketch of graphene p-n junction with a smooth interface. Panels (b)-(d) show the choice of primitive vectors and x,y axes when the interface is along the zigzag direction (b), the armchair direction (c), or a more general direction (d). The filled dots mark the Bravais lattice (A sublattice) of graphene. The shaded regions mark the unit cells. In panel (b), the X and Y axes of the Cartesian coordinate system are also shown.</figDesc><graphic coords="14,312.89,70.25,105.51,97.94" type="bitmap"/></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_10"><head/><label/><figDesc>)], where |a 1 | = |a 2 | = √ 3a C-C ≡ a and a C-C is the C-C bond length. The vanishingly small spinorbit coupling in graphene makes the GF spin-independent, so we neglect the electron spin. In the tight-binding model, each unit cell of graphene consists of M = 2 orbitals, i.e., |A,m,n and |B,m,n for the unit cell (m,n), where m (n) is the index along the x (y) axis of the tilted coordinate and A,B labels the sublattice [see Fig.7(c)]. The Hamiltonian Ĥ = Ĥ0 + V is the sum of the uniform partĤ0 = m,n t(|A,m + 1,n + |A,m,n -1 + |A,m,n ) B,m,n| + H.c.)(108)and the p-n junction potentialV = m,n V m (|A,m,n A,m,n| + |B,m,n B,m,n|), (109)where t ≈ 3 eV is the nearest-neighbor hopping constant<ref type="bibr" target="#b93">[94]</ref>. The junction potential V m depends arbitrarily on m inside the interface (m L m m R ), but equals V L inside the left lead L (m m L -1) and equals V R inside the right lead R (m m R + 1). Due to the invariance of Ĥ upon translation by |a 2 | along the y axis, the problem can be reduced from 2D to 1D by a Fourier transform |k y ≡ 1 N y n e ik y na |n , |n ≡ 1 N y k y e -ik y na |k y , (110) where N y is the number of unit cells along the y axis. In the new basis, the Hamiltonian Ĥ = k y Ĥ1D (k y )|k y k y | is diagonal with respect to k y , where Ĥ1D (k y ) describes a 1D lattice with the unit cells labeled by m and each unit cell containing 2 basis states |A ,|B . Let us use R mn ≡ ma 1 + na 2 to denote the Bravais vector of the unit cell (m,n) and use G(R m 2 n 2 ,R m 1 n 1 ,E) to denote the retarded GF from the unit cell (m 1 ,n 1 ) to the unit cell (m 2 ,n 2 ) of the original 2D system, which is connected to the retarded GF G m 2 ,m 1 (E,k y ) of the 1D lattice from the unit cell m 1 to the unit cell m 2 via a Fourier transform:</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_11"><head/><label/><figDesc>y ≡ k y (p = L,R). The GF from R m 1 n 1 to R m 2 n 2 can be measured as the conductance between one STM probe coupled to R m 1 n 1 and another STM probe coupled to R m 2 n 2 through the Landauer-Büttiker formula<ref type="bibr" target="#b0">[1]</ref> (2e 2 /h)T (E F ), where the transmission probability T</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_12"><head>+ R m 2 n 2 +R m 2 n 2 ˜R m 2 n 2 ≡</head><label>222</label><figDesc>(a)] shows imperfect focusing<ref type="bibr" target="#b83">[84]</ref> due to negative refraction across a finite-width p-n junction. Let us consider R m 2 n 2 and R m 1 n 1 both in the n region and R m 2 n 2 on the right ofR m 1 n 1 (i.e., m 2 &gt; m 1 ); the GF G R m 2 n 2 ,R m 1 n 1 (L,refl)+ is essential the sum of all right-going eigenmodes| (L) + (R m 2 n 2) and all reflection waves(L,refl) + e ik (L) -•(R m 2 n 2 -R m L ,0 ) | (L) -S (LL) e ik (L) + •(R m L,0 -R m 1 n 1 ) . (123)The incident wave contribution coincides with that of pristine graphene [Fig.10(b)]. The reflection wave contribution [Fig. 10(c)] tends to vanish perpendicularly to the junction interface, indicative of the chiral tunneling. The interference between the incident and reflection waves [Fig. 10(d)] is responsible for the interference pattern in the total GF [Fig. 10(a)], which would be directly manifested in dual-probe STM measurements.</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_13"><head>FIG. 10 .</head><label>10</label><figDesc>FIG.10. Contributions of different scattering channels to the Green's function G(R 2 ,R 1 ) for a smooth linear graphene p-n junction extending from 65 to 135 along the x axis (junction width ≈10 nm). Here R 1 ≡ (X 1 ,Y 1 ) is chosen to be fixed at (0,0) on the A sublattice, whileR 2 ≡ (X 2 ,Y 2 )is swept over all the B sublattice sites of the entire structure. (a) Contour plot of |G(R 2 ,R 1 )| vs R 2 -R 1 . Panels (b) and (c) extract the contributions to |G(R 2 ,R 1 )| from the incident wave and reflection wave, respectively. Panel (d) shows the contribution to |G(R 2 ,R 1 )| 2 due to the interference between the incident wave and the reflection wave.</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_14"><head>FIG. 11 .</head><label>11</label><figDesc>FIG. 11. Spatial map of the scaled conductance (i.e., the transmission coefficientT 12 times |R 2 -R 1 |) in a sharp graphene p-n junction as a function of R 2 -R 1 .Here R 1 ≡ (X 1 ,Y 1 ) is fixed at the A sublattice of the unit cell (0,0) and R 2 ≡ (X 2 ,Y 2 ) is swept over all the lattice sites (including both A and B sublattices) of the entire structure.</figDesc></figure>
<figure xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="fig_15"><head/><label/><figDesc>FIG.12. Transmission coefficient T 12 between two STM probes at mirror symmetric locations about the junction interface. (a) T 12 vs interprobe distance. (b) T 12 vs V 0 . Here, the width of the smooth junction is 5 nm for (a) and inset of (b), and the maximum of T 12 is always rescaled to 1 in each panel.</figDesc></figure>
		</body>
		<back>

			<div type="acknowledgement">
<div><head>ACKNOWLEDGMENTS</head><p>This work was supported by the <rs type="funder">MOST of China</rs> (Grants No. <rs type="grantNumber">2015CB921503</rs> and No. <rs type="grantNumber">2014CB848700</rs>), the <rs type="funder">NSFC</rs> (Grants No. <rs type="grantNumber">11274036</rs>, No. <rs type="grantNumber">11322542</rs>, No. <rs type="grantNumber">11434010</rs>, and No. <rs type="grantNumber">11504018</rs>), and the <rs type="funder">NSFC program for "Scientific Research Center"</rs> (Grant No. <rs type="grantNumber">U1530401</rs>). We acknowledge the computational support from the <rs type="funder">Beijing Computational Science Research Center (CSRC)</rs>.</p></div>
			</div>
			<listOrg type="funding">
				<org type="funding" xml:id="_mY9tCDh">
					<idno type="grant-number">2015CB921503</idno>
				</org>
				<org type="funding" xml:id="_VQmthgR">
					<idno type="grant-number">2014CB848700</idno>
				</org>
				<org type="funding" xml:id="_J3F2Stp">
					<idno type="grant-number">11274036</idno>
				</org>
				<org type="funding" xml:id="_W4CvCcT">
					<idno type="grant-number">11322542</idno>
				</org>
				<org type="funding" xml:id="_6wqC9PM">
					<idno type="grant-number">11434010</idno>
				</org>
				<org type="funding" xml:id="_DGsjU2p">
					<idno type="grant-number">11504018</idno>
				</org>
				<org type="funding" xml:id="_rj485Qa">
					<idno type="grant-number">U1530401</idno>
				</org>
			</listOrg>
			<div type="annex">
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>APPENDIX A: CALCULATION OF EIGENMODES</head><p>When the determinant of the M × M hopping matrix t † or t is nonzero, the 2M eigenmodes can be obtained by letting λ ≡ e ika and rewriting Eq. <ref type="bibr" target="#b19">(20)</ref> or equivalently [-t † + λ(zh)λ 2 t]| ≡ 0 as a generalized 2M × 2M eigenvalue problem</p><p>where z = E + i0 + . In the numerical calculation, we remove the infinitesimal imaginary part of z, i.e., z = E. Then Eq. (A1) is solved for 2M solutions {λ ≡ e ika ,| }, where k could be either real (traveling modes) or complex (evanescent modes).</p><p>Next the 2M eigenmodes are classified into M right-going ones and M left-going ones: the former consists of traveling modes (i.e., Im k = 0) with a positive group velocity and evanescent modes decaying exponentially to the right (i.e., Im k &gt; 0), while the latter consists of traveling modes (i.e., Im k = 0) with a negative group velocity and evanescent modes decaying exponentially to the left (i.e., Im k &lt; 0). There is an alternative but less accurate method to calculate and classify the eigenmodes. In this approach, the infinitesimal imaginary part of z is replaced by a finite but small positive number η, i.e., z = E + iη. Then Eq. (A1) is solved for the 2M solutions {λ ≡ e ika ,| }. Next, according to the sign of Im k, the 2M eigenmodes are classified into M right-going ones with Im k &gt; 0 and M left-going ones with Im k &lt; 0. In the limit η → 0 + , the imaginary part Im k may either vanish (i.e., traveling modes) or remain finite (i.e., evanescent modes). Obviously, the second approach is accurate only in the limit of η → 0 + , so we always use the first approach in the main text.</p><p>When the determinant of the hopping matrix t vanishes, solving Eq. (A1) would give some trivial evanescent eigenmodes. Suppose that M 0 out of the M eigenvalues of the hopping matrix t † or t are zero, and the corresponding eigenvectors are {| +,α } (for t † ) and {| -,α } (for t), where α = 1,2, . . . ,M 0 . Then there would be 2M 0 trivial evanescent eigenmodes, including M right-going ones λ +,α = 0,| +,α and M 0 left-going ones λ -,α = ∞, | -,α . The former correspond to <ref type="formula">19</ref>), while the latter correspond to <ref type="bibr" target="#b18">(19)</ref>. As a result, propagation matrices P -and P -1 + both diverge. However, this does not affect our formulas, which only contain P + and P -1  -due to causality. The only problem is that for a trivial evanescent eigenmode (s,α), the generalized group velocity v s,α [Eq. <ref type="bibr" target="#b87">(88)</ref>] is not well defined. For example, when λ +,α = 0 and hence λ -,α = ∞, the generalized velocity</p><p>This singular problem can be avoided by adding sufficiently small numbers { } to t and t † to make their determinant nonzero and take the limit { → 0} at the end of the calculation.</p><p>Taking the graphene junction as an example, the 1D left or right lead is characterized by the hopping matrix t and unit cell Hamiltonian V + h 0 , where V = V L (left lead) or V R (right lead) and h 0 , t are given by Eqs. (112) and (113).</p><p>Here the hopping matrix t has one zero eigenvalue with eigenvector | -,0 = [0,1] T , while t † has one zero eigenvalue with eigenvector | +,0 = [1,0] T . This gives rise to two trivial evanescent eigenmodes: the right-going one λ +,0 = 0,| +,0 and the left-going one λ -,0 = ∞, | -,0 , for which the generalized group velocities v +,0 = v * -,0 are not well defined. To cure this problem, we add a small number to the off-diagonal of the hopping matrix, so that t and t † become</p><p>Then using the first-order perturbation theory, we obtain</p><p>Substituting into Eq. ( <ref type="formula">88</ref>) and taking the limit → 0 gives v +,0 = v * -,0 = iat(e -iak y + 1). (A5)</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>APPENDIX B: SCATTERING OF A PARTIAL WAVE</head><p>Let us consider a scatterer connected to a semi-infinite left lead (whose conversion matrix is g) and prove that a rightgoing incident partial wave | in (m) is equivalent to a local excitation | loc m 0 ≡ g -1 | in (m 0 ) at an arbitrary site m 0 m L (m L is the left surface of the scatterer), in the sense that they produce the same scattering state at m m 0 . For this purpose, we use | (m) for the conventional scattering state emanating from the incident wave | in (m) and | (m) for the scattering state emanating from the local excitation | loc m 0 at m 0 . We notice that | (m) and | (m) obey the same Schrödinger equation for m m 0 + 1, and the same uniform Schrödinger equation</p><p>for m m 0 -1. The difference lies at m = m 0 :   <ref type="formula">46</ref>) and ( <ref type="formula">49</ref>) of the main text.</p></div>
<div xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0"><head>APPENDIX C: GREEN'S FUNCTION OF ONE SCATTERER: SIMPLE EXAMPLES</head><p>Here we give a few simple examples for the GF of an infinite (or semi-infinite) system containing a single scatterer. As the first example, a semi-infinite lead (with unit cell Hamiltonian h, hopping t, and propagation matrices P ± ) consisting of the unit cells m 0 can be regarded as a single-unit-cell scatterer at m = 0 connected to a semi-infinite left lead. Then the conversion matrix of this scatterer is</p><p>where we have used Eq. ( <ref type="formula">36</ref>) in the second step. The GF of the entire system is</p><p>Taking m = m 0 = 0 gives G (L) 0,0 = G (L) . By using Eqs. (C1) and ( <ref type="formula">35</ref>), we have G (L) g -1 -I = -P -1 -P + and hence recover the results by Sanvito et al. <ref type="bibr" target="#b40">[41]</ref>:</p><p>g. As the second example, a semi-infinite lead consisting of the unit cells m 0 can be regarded as a single-unit-cell scatterer at m = 0 connected to a semi-infinite right lead. Then the conversion matrix of this scatterer is</p><p>The GF of the entire system is</p><p>where G (R) g -1 -I = -P + P -1 -. Taking m = m 0 = 0 gives G (R)  0,0 = G (R) .</p><p>The third example is an interface at m = 0 (with unit cell Hamiltonian H 0,0 ) connected to two semi-infinite leads L and R. In this case the conversion matrix of the interface is</p><p>where t L (t R ) is the nearest-neighbor hopping in the left (right) lead. The GFs of the entire system are given by G m 0,m 0 0 = (P (R) + ) m G (I) (g (L) ) -1 g (L) 0,m 0 , (C6) G m 0,m 0 0 = (P (L) -) m G (I) (g (R) ) -1 g (R) 0,m 0 , (C7) G m 0,m 0 0 = g (L) m,m 0 + (P (L) -) m [G (I) (g (L) ) -1 -I]g (L) 0,m 0 , (C8) G m 0,m 0 0 = g (R)</p><p>m,m 0 + (P (R) + ) m [G (I) (g (R) ) -1 -I]g (R) 0,m 0 . (C9)</p></div>			</div>
			<div type="references">

				<listBibl>

<biblStruct xml:id="b0">
	<monogr>
		<title level="m" type="main">Electronic Transport in Mesoscopic Systems</title>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Datta</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<imprint>
			<date type="published" when="1995">1995</date>
			<publisher>Cambridge University Press</publisher>
			<pubPlace>Cambridge</pubPlace>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b1">
	<monogr>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><surname>Ferry</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Goodnick</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<title level="m">Transport in Nanostructures</title>
		<meeting><address><addrLine>Cambridge</addrLine></address></meeting>
		<imprint>
			<publisher>Cambridge University Press</publisher>
			<date type="published" when="1997">1997</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b2">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Y</forename><surname>Blanter</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Büttiker</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1016/S0370-1573(99)00123-4</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rep</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">336</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2000">2000</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b3">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Cresti</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><surname>Farchioni</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G</forename><surname>Grosso</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G</forename><forename type="middle">P</forename><surname>Parravicini</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.68.075306</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">68</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">75306</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2003">2003</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b4">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G</forename><surname>Metalidis</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Bruno</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.72.235304</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">72</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">235304</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2005">2005</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b5">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><surname>Landauer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1147/rd.13.0223</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">IBM J. Res. Dev</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">1</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">223</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1957">1957</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b6">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><surname>Landauer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1080/14786437008238472</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Philos. Mag</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">21</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">863</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1970">1970</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b7">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Büttiker</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Y</forename><surname>Imry</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><surname>Landauer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Pinhas</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.31.6207</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">31</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">6207</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1985">1985</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b8">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Khomyakov</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G</forename><surname>Brocks</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.70.195402</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">70</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">195402</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2004">2004</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b9">
	<monogr>
		<title level="m" type="main">Electronic Structure and the Properties of Solids</title>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">W</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Harrison</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<imprint>
			<date type="published" when="1989">1989</date>
			<publisher>Dover</publisher>
			<pubPlace>New York</pubPlace>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b10">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Kudrnovský</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><surname>Drchal</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">I</forename><surname>Turek</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Weinberger</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.50.16105</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">50</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">16105</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1994">1994</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b11">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><surname>Zeller</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Dederichs</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><surname>Újfalussy</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">L</forename><surname>Szunyogh</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Weinberger</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.52.8807</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">52</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">8807</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1995">1995</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b12">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><surname>Caroli</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><surname>Combescot</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Nozieres</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><surname>Saint-James</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1088/0022-3719/4/8/018</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Phys. C</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">4</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">916</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1971">1971</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b13">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><forename type="middle">S</forename><surname>Fisher</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Lee</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.23.6851</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">23</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">6851</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1981">1981</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b14">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">D</forename><surname>Stone</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Szafer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1147/rd.323.0384</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">IBM J. Res. Dev</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">32</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">384</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1988">1988</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b15">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">H</forename><forename type="middle">U</forename><surname>Baranger</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">D</forename><surname>Stone</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.40.8169</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">40</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">8169</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1989">1989</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b16">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><surname>Sols</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1016/S0003-4916(05)80005-3</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Ann. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">214</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">386</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1992">1992</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b17">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Lewenkopf</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><forename type="middle">R</forename><surname>Mucciolo</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1007/s10825-013-0458-7</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Comput. Electron</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">12</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">203</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2013">2013</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b18">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Drouvelis</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Schmelcher</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Bastian</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1016/j.jcp.2005.11.010</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Comput. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">215</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">741</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2006">2006</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b19">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><forename type="middle">J</forename><surname>Thouless</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Kirkpatrick</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1088/0022-3719/14/3/007</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Phys. C</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">14</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">235</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1981">1981</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b20">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Lee</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><forename type="middle">S</forename><surname>Fisher</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevLett.47.882</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">47</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">882</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1981">1981</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b21">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Mackinnon</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1007/BF01328846</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Z. Phys. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">59</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">385</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1985">1985</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b22">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">H</forename><forename type="middle">U</forename><surname>Baranger</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><forename type="middle">P</forename><surname>Divincenzo</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Jalabert</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">D</forename><surname>Stone</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.44.10637</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">44</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">10637</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1991">1991</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b23">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><surname>Kazymyrenko</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">X</forename></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.77.115119</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">77</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">115119</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2008">2008</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b24">
	<monogr>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Wimmer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<imprint>
			<date type="published" when="2009">2009</date>
		</imprint>
		<respStmt>
			<orgName>University of Regensburg</orgName>
		</respStmt>
	</monogr>
	<note>Ph.D. thesis</note>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b25">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">X</forename><surname>Zheng</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S.-H</forename><surname>Ke</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">W</forename><surname>Yang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1063/1.3357416</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Chem. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">132</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">114703</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2010">2010</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b26">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Settnes</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><forename type="middle">R</forename><surname>Power</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Lin</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Petersen</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A.-P</forename><surname>Jauho</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.91.125408</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">91</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">125408</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2015">2015</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b27">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Mackinnon</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><surname>Kramer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevLett.47.1546</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">47</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1546</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1981">1981</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b28">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Soukoulis</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">I</forename><surname>Webman</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G</forename><forename type="middle">S</forename><surname>Grest</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><forename type="middle">N</forename><surname>Economou</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.26.1838</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">26</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1838</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1982">1982</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b29">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Mackinnon</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><surname>Kramer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1007/BF01578242</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Z. Phys. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">53</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1983">1983</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b30">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">L</forename><surname>Schweitzer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><surname>Kramer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Mackinnon</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1088/0022-3719/17/23/012</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Phys. C</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">17</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">4111</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1984">1984</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b31">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><forename type="middle">P L</forename><surname>Sancho</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">M L</forename><surname>Sancho</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Rubio</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1088/0305-4608/14/5/016</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Phys. F</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">14</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1205</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1984">1984</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b32">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><forename type="middle">P L</forename><surname>Sancho</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">M L</forename><surname>Sancho</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Rubio</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1088/0305-4608/15/4/009</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Phys. F</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">15</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">851</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1985">1985</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b33">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">H</forename><surname>Aoki</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Ando</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevLett.54.831</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">54</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">831</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1985">1985</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b34">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Ando</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.40.5325</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">40</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">5325</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1989">1989</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b35">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><surname>Sols</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Macucci</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">U</forename><surname>Ravaioli</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><surname>Hess</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1063/1.344032</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Appl. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">66</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">3892</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1989">1989</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b36">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Ando</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.42.5626</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">42</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">5626</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1990">1990</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b37">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Godfrin</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1088/0953-8984/3/40/005</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Phys.: Condens. Matter</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">3</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">7843</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1991">1991</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b38">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><forename type="middle">Buongiorno</forename><surname>Nardelli</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.60.7828</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">60</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">7828</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1999">1999</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b39">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Umerski</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.55.5266</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">55</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">5266</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1997">1997</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b40">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Sanvito</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><forename type="middle">J</forename><surname>Lambert</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Jefferson</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Bratkovsky</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.59.11936</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">59</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">11936</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1999">1999</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b41">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><surname>Garcia-Moliner</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><surname>Velasco</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1016/0039-6028(94)90665-3</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Surf. Sci</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">299</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">332</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1994">1994</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b42">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Vasseur</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Akjouj</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">L</forename><surname>Dobrzynski</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><surname>Djafari-Rouhani</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><forename type="middle">E</forename><surname>Boudouti</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1016/j.surfrep.2004.04.001</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Surf. Sci. Rep</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">54</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2004">2004</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b43">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">R</forename><surname>Rocha</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Sanvito</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.70.094406</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">70</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">94406</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2004">2004</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b44">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Brandbyge</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J.-L</forename><surname>Mozos</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Ordejón</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Taylor</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><surname>Stokbro</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.65.165401</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">65</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">165401</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2002">2002</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b45">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">R</forename><surname>Rocha</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>García-Suárez</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Bailey</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><surname>Lambert</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Ferrer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Sanvito</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.73.085414</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">73</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">85414</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2006">2006</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b46">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Birner</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Zibold</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Andlauer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Kubis</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Sabathil</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Trellakis</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Vogl</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1109/TED.2007.902871</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">IEEE Trans. Electron Dev</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">54</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">2137</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2007">2007</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b47">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Ozaki</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><surname>Nishio</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">H</forename><surname>Kino</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.81.035116</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">81</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">35116</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2010">2010</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b48">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">E</forename><surname>Fonseca</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Kubis</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Povolotskyi</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><surname>Novakovic</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Ajoy</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G</forename><surname>Hegde</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">H</forename><surname>Ilatikhameneh</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Z</forename><surname>Jiang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Sengupta</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Y</forename><surname>Tan</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1007/s10825-013-0509-0</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Comput. Electron</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">12</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">592</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2013">2013</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b49">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><forename type="middle">W</forename><surname>Groth</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Wimmer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">R</forename><surname>Akhmerov</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">X</forename><surname>Waintal</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1088/1367-2630/16/6/063065</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">New J. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">16</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">63065</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2014">2014</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b50">
	<monogr>
		<title level="m" type="main">Superlattices Microstruct</title>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Datta</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1006/spmi.2000.0920</idno>
		<imprint>
			<date type="published" when="2000">2000</date>
			<biblScope unit="volume">28</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">253</biblScope>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b51">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Ando</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.44.8017</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">44</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">8017</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1991">1991</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b52">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><surname>Nikolić</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Mackinnon</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.50.11008</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">50</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">11008</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1994">1994</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b53">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><surname>Xia</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Zwierzycki</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Talanana</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><forename type="middle">J</forename><surname>Kelly</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G</forename><forename type="middle">E W</forename><surname>Bauer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.73.064420</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">73</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">64420</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2006">2006</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b54">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Khomyakov</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G</forename><surname>Brocks</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><surname>Karpan</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Zwierzycki</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><forename type="middle">J</forename><surname>Kelly</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.72.035450</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">72</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">35450</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2005">2005</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b55">
	<monogr>
		<title level="m" type="main">describes the scattering of both traveling and evanescent waves, while S(E) only describes the scattering of traveling waves</title>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G(e)</forename><surname>Since</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<imprint/>
	</monogr>
	<note>G(E) and S(E) are equivalent only in the asymptotic regions of the lead, i.e., sufficiently far way from the scatterer such that the evanescent waves vanish completely</note>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b56">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Nakayama</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">O</forename><surname>Kubo</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Y</forename><surname>Shingaya</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Higuchi</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Hasegawa</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C.-S</forename><surname>Jiang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Okuda</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Y</forename><surname>Kuwahara</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><surname>Takami</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Aono</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1002/adma.201200257</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Adv. Mater</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">24</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1675</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2012">2012</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b57">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A.-P</forename><surname>Li</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><forename type="middle">W</forename><surname>Clark</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">X.-G</forename><surname>Zhang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">P</forename><surname>Baddorf</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1002/adfm.201203423</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Adv. Funct. Mater</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">23</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">2509</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2013">2013</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b58">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">O</forename><surname>Kubo</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Y</forename><surname>Shingaya</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Nakaya</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Aono</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Nakayama</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1063/1.2213954</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Appl. Phys. Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">88</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">254101</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2006">2006</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b59">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><surname>Cherepanov</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><surname>Zubkov</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">H</forename><surname>Junker</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Korte</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Blab</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Coenen</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><surname>Voigtländer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1063/1.3694990</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Rev. Sci. Instrum</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">83</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">33707</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2012">2012</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b60">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Qin</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T.-H</forename><surname>Kim</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Z</forename><surname>Wang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A.-P</forename><surname>Li</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1063/1.4727878</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Rev. Sci. Instrum</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">83</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">63704</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2012">2012</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b61">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">H</forename><surname>Watanabe</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><surname>Manabe</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Shigematsu</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Shimizu</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1063/1.1371529</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Appl. Phys. Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">78</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">2928</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2001">2001</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b62">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Baringhaus</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Ruan</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><surname>Edler</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Tejeda</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Sicot</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Taleb-Ibrahimi</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A.-P</forename><surname>Li</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Z</forename><surname>Jiang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Conrad</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><surname>Berger</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1038/nature12952</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Nature</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">506</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">349</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2014">2014</date>
			<pubPlace>London</pubPlace>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b63">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Baringhaus</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Settnes</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Aprojanz</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><forename type="middle">R</forename><surname>Power</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A.-P</forename><surname>Jauho</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><surname>Tegenkamp</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevLett.116.186602</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">116</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">186602</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2016">2016</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b64">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><forename type="middle">W</forename><surname>Sutter</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J.-I</forename><surname>Flege</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Sutter</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1038/nmat2166</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Nat. Mater</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">7</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">406</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2008">2008</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b65">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S.-H</forename><surname>Ji</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">B</forename><surname>Hannon</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Tromp</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><surname>Perebeinos</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Tersoff</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Ross</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1038/nmat3170</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Nat. Mater</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">11</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">114</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2012">2012</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b66">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><forename type="middle">R</forename><surname>Eder</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Kotakoski</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><surname>Holzweber</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><surname>Mangler</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><surname>Skakalova</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">C</forename><surname>Meyer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1021/nl3042799</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Nano Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">13</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1934</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2013">2013</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b67">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><forename type="middle">W</forename><surname>Clark</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">X.-G</forename><surname>Zhang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">I</forename><forename type="middle">V</forename><surname>Vlassiouk</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G</forename><surname>He</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Feenstra</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A.-P</forename><surname>Li</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1021/nn403056k</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">ACS Nano</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">7</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">7956</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2013">2013</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b68">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><forename type="middle">W</forename><surname>Clark</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">X.-G</forename><surname>Zhang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G</forename><surname>Gu</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Park</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G</forename><surname>He</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Feenstra</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A.-P</forename><surname>Li</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevX.4.011021</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. X</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">4</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">11021</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2014">2014</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b69">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T.-H</forename><surname>Kim</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">X.-G</forename><surname>Zhang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Nicholson</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Evans</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">N</forename><forename type="middle">S</forename><surname>Kulkarni</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><surname>Radhakrishnan</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Kenik</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A.-P</forename><surname>Li</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1021/nl101734h</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Nano Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">10</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">3096</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2010">2010</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b70">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Settnes</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><forename type="middle">R</forename><surname>Power</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Petersen</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A.-P</forename><surname>Jauho</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevLett.112.096801</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">112</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">96801</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2014">2014</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b71">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Rotter</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J.-Z</forename><surname>Tang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">L</forename><surname>Wirtz</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Trost</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Burgdörfer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.62.1950</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">62</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1950</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2000">2000</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b72">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Maao</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">I</forename><forename type="middle">V</forename><surname>Zozulenko</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Hauge</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.50.17320</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">50</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">17320</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1994">1994</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b73">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">I</forename><forename type="middle">V</forename><surname>Zozoulenko</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Maao</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Hauge</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.53.7975</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">53</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">7975</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1996">1996</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b74">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">I</forename><forename type="middle">V</forename><surname>Zozoulenko</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Maao</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Hauge</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.53.7987</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">53</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">7987</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1996">1996</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b75">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M.-H</forename><surname>Liu</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><surname>Richter</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.86.115455</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">86</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">115455</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2012">2012</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b76">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><forename type="middle">S</forename><surname>Krstić</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">X.-G</forename><surname>Zhang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">W</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Butler</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.66.205319</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">66</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">205319</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2002">2002</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b77">
	<monogr>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">J</forename><surname>Sakurai</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Napolitano</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<title level="m">Modern Quantum Mechanics</title>
		<imprint>
			<publisher>San Fransisco</publisher>
			<date type="published" when="2011">2011</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
	<note>nd ed.</note>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b78">
	<monogr>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><forename type="middle">J</forename><surname>Griffiths</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<title level="m">Introduction to Quantum Mechanics</title>
		<meeting><address><addrLine>Upper Saddle River, NJ</addrLine></address></meeting>
		<imprint>
			<publisher>Prentice Hall</publisher>
			<date type="published" when="1995">1995</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b79">
	<monogr>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><surname>Cohen-Tannoudji</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><surname>Diu</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><surname>Laloe</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<title level="m">Quantum Mechanics</title>
		<meeting><address><addrLine>New York</addrLine></address></meeting>
		<imprint>
			<publisher>Wiley-VCH</publisher>
			<date type="published" when="2005">2005</date>
			<biblScope unit="volume">2</biblScope>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
	<note>nd ed.</note>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b80">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">O</forename><surname>Klein</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1007/BF01339716</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Z. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">53</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">157</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1929">1929</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b81">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><forename type="middle">I</forename><surname>Katsnelson</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><forename type="middle">S</forename><surname>Novoselov</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">K</forename><surname>Geim</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1038/nphys384</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Nat. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">2</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">620</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2006">2006</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b82">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><forename type="middle">V</forename><surname>Cheianov</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><forename type="middle">I</forename><surname>Fal'ko</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.74.041403</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">74</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">41403</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2006">2006</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b83">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><forename type="middle">V</forename><surname>Cheianov</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><forename type="middle">L</forename><surname>Altshuler</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1126/science.1138020</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Science</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">315</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1252</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2007">2007</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b84">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C.-H</forename><surname>Park</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Y.-W</forename><surname>Son</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">L</forename><surname>Yang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><forename type="middle">L</forename><surname>Cohen</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><forename type="middle">G</forename><surname>Louie</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1021/nl801752r</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Nano Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">8</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">2920</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2008">2008</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b85">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">G</forename><surname>Moghaddam</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Zareyan</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevLett.105.146803</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">105</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">146803</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2010">2010</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b86">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G.-H</forename><surname>Lee</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">G.-H</forename><surname>Park</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">H.-J</forename><surname>Lee</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1038/nphys3460</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Nat. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">11</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">925</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2015">2015</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b87">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Chen</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Z</forename><surname>Han</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Elahi</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><forename type="middle">M M</forename><surname>Habib</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">L</forename><surname>Wang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B</forename><surname>Wen</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Y</forename><surname>Gao</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Taniguchi</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><surname>Watanabe</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Hone</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1126/science.aaf5481</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Science</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">353</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1522</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2016">2016</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b88">
	<monogr>
		<title level="m" type="main">Lattice models with hopping between pth nearest neighbors can always be reduced to nearest-neighbor hopping by regarding p successive unit cells as one composite unit cell</title>
		<imprint/>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b89">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Velev</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">W</forename><surname>Butler</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1088/0953-8984/16/21/R01</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Phys.: Condens. Matter</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">16</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2004">2004</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b90">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Lee</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">D</forename><surname>Joannopoulos</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.23.4997</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">23</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">4997</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1981">1981</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b91">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">L</forename><surname>Molinari</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1088/0305-4470/30/3/021</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">J. Phys. A: Math. Gen</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">30</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">983</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1997">1997</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b92">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><forename type="middle">W J</forename><surname>Beenakker</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/RevModPhys.80.1337</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Rev. Mod. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">80</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">1337</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2008">2008</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b93">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Castro Neto</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><surname>Guinea</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">N</forename><forename type="middle">M R</forename><surname>Peres</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><forename type="middle">S</forename><surname>Novoselov</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">K</forename><surname>Geim</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/RevModPhys.81.109</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Rev. Mod. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">81</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">109</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2009">2009</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b94">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">N</forename><forename type="middle">M R</forename><surname>Peres</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/RevModPhys.82.2673</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Rev. Mod. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">82</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">2673</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2010">2010</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b95">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><forename type="middle">Das</forename><surname>Sarma</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Adam</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Hwang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">E</forename><surname>Rossi</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/RevModPhys.83.407</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Rev. Mod. Phys</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">83</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">407</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2011">2011</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b96">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><forename type="middle">E</forename><surname>Allain</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><surname>Fuchs</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1140/epjb/e2011-20351-3</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Eur. Phys. J. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">83</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">301</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2011">2011</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b97">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><forename type="middle">G</forename><surname>Veselago</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1070/PU1968v010n04ABEH003699</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Sov. Phys. Usp</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">10</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">509</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="1968">1968</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b98">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">B</forename><surname>Pendry</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevLett.85.3966</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">85</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">3966</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2000">2000</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b99">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">X</forename><surname>Zhang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">Z</forename><surname>Liu</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1038/nmat2141</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Nat. Mater</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">7</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">435</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2008">2008</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b100">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">B</forename><surname>Pendry</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><surname>Aubry</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><forename type="middle">R</forename><surname>Smith</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Maier</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1126/science.1220600</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Science</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">337</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">549</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2012">2012</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b101">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">L</forename><surname>Zhao</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Tang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">B.-L</forename><surname>Gu</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">W</forename><surname>Duan</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevLett.111.116601</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">111</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">116601</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2013">2013</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b102">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Pereira</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">V</forename><surname>Mlinar</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">F</forename><forename type="middle">M</forename><surname>Peeters</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><surname>Vasilopoulos</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.74.045424</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">74</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">45424</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2006">2006</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b103">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Downing</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><forename type="middle">E</forename><surname>Portnoi</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevA.90.052116</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. A</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">90</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">52116</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2014">2014</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b104">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><surname>Logemann</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><forename type="middle">J A</forename><surname>Reijnders</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">T</forename><surname>Tudorovskiy</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><forename type="middle">I</forename><surname>Katsnelson</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><surname>Yuan</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.91.045420</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">91</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">45420</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2015">2015</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b105">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Bardarson</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Titov</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">P</forename><forename type="middle">W</forename><surname>Brouwer</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevLett.102.226803</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. Lett</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">102</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">226803</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2009">2009</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b106">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">C</forename><forename type="middle">A</forename><surname>Downing</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A</forename><forename type="middle">R</forename><surname>Pearce</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">R</forename><forename type="middle">J</forename><surname>Churchill</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><forename type="middle">E</forename><surname>Portnoi</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.92.165401</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">92</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">165401</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2015">2015</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b107">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">M</forename><surname>Settnes</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S</forename><forename type="middle">R</forename><surname>Power</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">D</forename><forename type="middle">H</forename><surname>Petersen</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">A.-P</forename><surname>Jauho</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.90.035440</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">90</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">35440</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2014">2014</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

<biblStruct xml:id="b108">
	<analytic>
		<title/>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">S.-H</forename><surname>Zhang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">J.-J</forename><surname>Zhu</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">W</forename><surname>Yang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">H.-Q</forename><surname>Lin</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<author>
			<persName><forename type="first">K</forename><surname>Chang</surname></persName>
		</author>
		<idno type="DOI">10.1103/PhysRevB.94.085408</idno>
	</analytic>
	<monogr>
		<title level="j">Phys. Rev. B</title>
		<imprint>
			<biblScope unit="volume">94</biblScope>
			<biblScope unit="page">85408</biblScope>
			<date type="published" when="2016">2016</date>
		</imprint>
	</monogr>
</biblStruct>

				</listBibl>
			</div>
		</back>
	</text>
</TEI>